<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Milwaukee on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/milwaukee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Milwaukee on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 07:10:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/milwaukee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A 21 Year Old Friendship</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 07:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</guid>
      <description>Krishnamurthy. He is my oldest friend. We were in same class in Bangalore for six years starting 1990 before I had to leave. We were not in touch and had not met more than a handful of times in the last fifteen years. Then when I met him, he was still the same! He had moved to a new place and before I knew it, he was gone from there. I tried to find him but in vain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm The Bastille 2011 - Milwaukee</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/storm-the-bastille-2011-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 05:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/storm-the-bastille-2011-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>The Bastille, the medieval fortress and prison in Paris, was stormed by the demonstrators to acquire the ammunition on 14 July 1789. This day marks the start of the French Revolution and is celebrated as a national holiday in France. The same is celebrated in across the world. One such place is Milwaukee. Yes, the place I live now!
 Bastille Days is North America&amp;rsquo;s largest outdoor French themed festival held in downtown Milwaukee in Cathedral Square Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northwestern Mutual Supports Green Bay Packers</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 05:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</guid>
      <description>Pictures of Northwestern Mutual Insurance company in downtown Milwaukee during NFL 2011 showing support for Green Bay Packers.
  Northwestern Mutual East Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee
    Northwestern Mutual South Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee
   Photo courtesy: Sushanth Mohan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From India To USA</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-india-to-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-india-to-usa/</guid>
      <description>I can write a detailed travelogue, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to bore you to death! I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m good at writing! Here is the short version! 😃
A weeks notice was all I got about my first ever business trip. To work at client&amp;rsquo;s location, to deal with client interaction, to deal with the cultural differences, and the list goes on. Though I was prepared for all of it, I was caught off guard with other stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>