<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>todo on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/todo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in todo on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 20:58:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/todo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HOLY CRAP!!!</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holy-crap-missing-in-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 20:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holy-crap-missing-in-action/</guid>
      <description>HOLY MOTHER OF SWEET BABY CORN! It has seriously been a long while! 3 years? 4 years? Surprised the blog still exists! LOL! Actually not that much surprised. I pay every year to renew hosting so I know it exists! 😛
The TODO list thing I do. Seriously, it has gotten out of hand! I have unfinished drafts from 2011, 2012, 2013 which are still not posted! I feel embarrassed; at the same time I feel overwhelmed thinking how fast the time flies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Have I Been Up To This Summer?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 17:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>It has been a long time since I blogged regularly. We have a couple of weeks of summer left in 2012 and I don’t want to waste that spending more time on blogging. Lately, I have been feeling like blogging is a winter activity (not saying that I blog regularly in winter). There are a number of topics blog about but no time. I keep adding topics to the todo list and keep deleting when I revisit because it’s either too late or it is making the list too big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working on The Blog</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/working-on-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 09:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/working-on-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>This is a perfect example for a seemingly easy task taking up so much of one&#39;s time. I have been busy working on this blog for a last couple of days. I spent so much time and yet there are so many things to do!
Here is what I have done so far:
  Updated feed through FeedBurner: this was already present, I updated some settings.
  Added Google AdSense: there comes a time in everyone&#39;s life when they turn greedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2010 - A Long Weekend</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/thanksgiving-2010-a-long-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 01:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/thanksgiving-2010-a-long-weekend/</guid>
      <description>A long weekend (four days) - many of my friends are on trips visiting places. I&#39;m sitting here writing this post! I couldn&#39;t go due to work. I had to work for a couple of hours exactly in the middle of the four days so I stayed back. It sure doesn&#39;t feel good but not as bad as I imagined it to be. Almost 3/4th of the long weekend has gone by.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>