<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>India on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/india/</link>
    <description>Recent content in India on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 05:47:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/india/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Blue/Light Blue Maps of India</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/dark-blue-light-blue-maps-of-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 05:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/dark-blue-light-blue-maps-of-india/</guid>
      <description>These are the India maps I created* when designing my homepage for the grand 2011 Cricket World Cup.
I had a tough time searching for a blue map of India online and ended up creating them myself. With this post they are released online; you are free to use them as you may wish. However, a link to this blog is really appreciated (which I&#39;m sure none of you are going to do!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indians Are The World Champions</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 06:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</guid>
      <description>You know by now. Indians are the world champions! Yeah, say that again, WE ARE THE CHAMPIONS!
Remember &amp;ldquo;More than a billion hearts and one shared dream&amp;rdquo;? That&#39;s what I wrote when the world cup started. That dream has come true! Now more than 50% of Indian population can proudly say they saw their captain lift the world cup at least once in their life. Glory!
Homepage mania: I dedicated the homepage to Green Bay Packers and they won the super bowl; they are the Champions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2011 World Cup</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/</guid>
      <description>My dear fellow Indians and everyone,
Remember 1983 Prudential world cup? Remember Captain Kapil Dev&#39;s greatest catch that dethroned King Viv? No? Neither do I! It&#39;s been 28 years since our captain lifted the cricket world cup. Not just me, nearly 50% of the current Indian population wasn&#39;t even born back then!
More than a billion hearts and one shared dream, to see the men in blue lift the 2011 cricket world cup.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>