<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Niagara on Praveen Lobo</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/niagara/</link><description>Recent content in Niagara on Praveen Lobo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 02:51:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/niagara/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 02:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="niagara-new-york-united-states">Niagara, New York, United States&lt;/h4>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/29-niagara/Terrapin%20Point%202.jpg"
 alt="Terrapin Point, Goat Island">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Terrapin Point, Goat Island&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>The next day as planned we drove to Niagara falls. There were a lot of people; I could see a lot of Indians as well. You probably won&amp;rsquo;t believe me but I met my a friend from my college (India) with his friends on Goat Island, I had no clue he was also visiting. Then I met another friend of mine from Bangalore on the Observation Tower! My friends were right when they said be prepared to see the place full of &lt;em>desis&lt;/em>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 04:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="cedar-point-sandusky-ohio-united-states">Cedar Point, Sandusky, Ohio, United States.&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>During the long weekend of September 2010, I visited Cedar Point and Niagara falls along with three other friends. It was an awesome trip. We took a flight from Milwaukee to Cleveland Ohio and rented a car from airport for the entire trip. The plan was to go to Cedar Point one day, visit Niagara next day, and head back the day after.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>First we drove to Cedar Point (Sandusky Ohio) from Marriott (Cleveland Airport Marriott). It was already noon by the time we reached there. It looked a bit scary from outside. All those roller coasters, best in America rankings, and &lt;em>never-before-sat-in-a-roller-coaster&lt;/em> feeling. Once we were inside there were huge lines near all coasters and rides. It was obvious that we would not be able to cover all of it especially because my friend and I wanted to sit at the very front in all rides that we take that day. So, we decided to hit the best of Cedar Point.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>