<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Skydive on Praveen Lobo</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/skydive/</link><description>Recent content in Skydive on Praveen Lobo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 05:40:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/skydive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Was My Skydiving All About?</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 05:40:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ever since I posted my skydiving post/video and dedicated it to the people fighting against corruption, some of my friends have been teasing me about it. I did what I wanted to and have no regrets. I have been able to shut them up with just asking if they have the balls to do it before talking smack!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I can take a good tease but the attitude of getting things done quickly and avoiding lines even if it means paying bribe irks me to the core. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind having a healthy discussion, but with some so determined to pay bribe to get things done quickly and wholeheartedly oppose anyone who fights corruption, any discussion is a waste of time and energy. Many of my American friends are optimistic and talk positively (esp. knowing the Gandhi episode), but many of my own countrymen are very very skeptical and pessimistic. If well educated people don&amp;rsquo;t support a cause and act overly smart, what do you think will change? Everything has to start some way and someday, why not make this a starting point for a good future?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Do It Now, or You Might Never Get A Chance Again</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/do-it-now-or-you-might-never-get-a-chance-again/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 05:58:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/do-it-now-or-you-might-never-get-a-chance-again/</guid><description>&lt;p>Finally on August 20th, 2011, I skydived for the first time, not only unheeding my friends&amp;rsquo; suggestions to go for tandem first and then solo/Accelerated Free Fall (AFF) but also my own fear of jumping into the unknown. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how it will be to fall from 14,000 feet, descending at 120MPH (193KMPH). I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if the instructors will be able to guide me ntil the pull; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if the parachute will open fine or not; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if I would land on Interstate-94 and get dragged down the road.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>One Hell Of A Tiring Weekend</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/one-hell-of-a-tiring-weekend-skydive-plan-gone-wrong-and-lake-geneva-again/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 03:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/one-hell-of-a-tiring-weekend-skydive-plan-gone-wrong-and-lake-geneva-again/</guid><description>&lt;p>If everything went according to the plan, I&amp;rsquo;d have had my first ever free-fall by now. But the mother nature had some other plans. Six friends and I had planned for a skydiving weekend on my room-mate&amp;rsquo;s birthday last Saturday. Two of them had come down from Chicago. The venue was none other than the closest &lt;a href="http://www.skydivemidwest.com/">Skydive Midwest&lt;/a>. None of us had previous experience and were looking forward to having a great time. We reached the place a couple of minutes after our scheduled time and registered at the manifest. Basically, we just put our lives on the line and signed contracts saying Skydive Midwest will not be liable for any accidents. Six of us were to do tandem jumps and I solo (Accelerated Free Fall - AFF). Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me why I decided to jump solo; I don&amp;rsquo;t know!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>