<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bicycle on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/bicycle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bicycle on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 16:46:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/bicycle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ride Lobo Ride - UPAF Ride For The Arts 2012</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/ride-lobo-ride-upaf-ride-for-the-arts-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 16:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/ride-lobo-ride-upaf-ride-for-the-arts-2012/</guid>
      <description>Over quarter of a million participants have taken part in annual United Performing Arts Fund (UPAF) Ride for the Arts since 1981. According to UPAF, which provides financial support to 36 beneficiary groups, the ride helps keep the performing arts scene dynamic and a vital part of the community&amp;rsquo;s culture and that they are among the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest united arts funds in terms of dollars raised and number of donors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Second Bicycle</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-second-bicycle-a-2012-trek-ds-8-3-bicycle-from-wheel-and-sprocket-bike-expo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 03:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-second-bicycle-a-2012-trek-ds-8-3-bicycle-from-wheel-and-sprocket-bike-expo/</guid>
      <description>I used to love bicycles until I started working and moved on to ride motorbikes. Motorbikes were convenient, affordable, and fast. I had bought myself a TVS Suzuki Fiero DS (India&amp;rsquo;s first 150cc bike I think) and I was using it for everyday commute. I had sold my first bicycle and didn&amp;rsquo;t have one to ride. As it happens as one grows up, I had given up on bicycles.
After moving to US, I live very close walk to work and don&amp;rsquo;t need any vehicles for travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Bicycle - An Hercules MTB</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-bicycle-hercules-mtb-bangalore-year-2000/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 01:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-bicycle-hercules-mtb-bangalore-year-2000/</guid>
      <description>As a kid I was jealous of my brother, my cousin, and all my friends (who knew how to ride a bicycle). I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to ride a bike until I was thirteen or fourteen I think. My mom was too scared to allow me to ride a bicycle. I&amp;rsquo;d lie to mom and go trying to ride a bike instead of playing. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember anyone helping me how to ride.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>