<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Current Affairs on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/current-affairs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Current Affairs on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 22:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/current-affairs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes you have to talk politics with friends</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/sometimes-you-have-to-talk-politics-with-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/sometimes-you-have-to-talk-politics-with-friends/</guid>
      <description>::backstory
 Just because you do not take an interest in politics doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean politics won&amp;rsquo;t take an interest in you. Pericles  :: Petrol has gone up image
reporduced wihtout names
[9:14 AM, 5/24/2018] Praveen Lobo: Little does he know that ancient India had aircrafts that didn&amp;rsquo;t even need petrol. Our PM is digging to find more evidence. 😜 [9:15 AM, 5/24/2018] Praveen Lobo: Also, no links. No timestamp. Looks like subtle propoganda for 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Presidential Elections</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/us-presidential-election-2016-trump-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 03:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/us-presidential-election-2016-trump-card/</guid>
      <description>The 2016 US presidential election campaigns are underway, and they are very entertaining! I do not know to the full extent how this entire presidential election works. I doubt if many of the US citizens even understand how this works! So, I spent a couple of hours on this topic and decided to write about it. If you find any inaccuracies, I will be glad to fix it!
US presidential elections are important not just for the Americans but also for the rest of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Paid A Bribe Once</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-paid-a-bribe-once/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 05:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-paid-a-bribe-once/</guid>
      <description>When I was growing up, I used to read the articles in the newspaper about people returning the money/jewelry that somebody else had lost, the auto driver returning thousands of rupees the passengers had left behind. I used to wonder what made them do what they did especially when the person who did it was indeed very poor. Why didn&amp;rsquo;t s/he keep it her/himself, used it to feed his family, made a life out of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strike Out Corruption In India</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/strike-out-corruption-in-india-support-jan-lokpal-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 07:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/strike-out-corruption-in-india-support-jan-lokpal-bill/</guid>
      <description>CORRUPTION IN INDIA
Will Jan Lokpal bill solve the issue? I don&amp;rsquo;t know for sure, but it will definitely set us on the right path by giving more power to those who matter. It&amp;rsquo;s heartening to see India united to fight against the corruption. If an old man [Anna Hazare] can do so much, why can&amp;rsquo;t the youth do more? If you can, PLEASE SHOW YOUR SUPPORT in any way possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBMP Elections and Women Reservation</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/bbmp-elections-and-women-reservation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 19:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/bbmp-elections-and-women-reservation/</guid>
      <description>BBMP elections are scheduled for tomorrow. My ward is one of those wards reserved for women. That is nothing to be happy about! Reservation is a very noble plan with a pathetic implementation. I was trying to get as much information about the candidates as possible so that I can vote for the most eligible. There are seven women candidates contesting in the election from my ward. As far as I could see, all of them are wives or relatives of politically powerful men and I find most of them incapable!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>