<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ski on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/ski/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ski on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 04:53:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/ski/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skiing on Cascade mountains, Wisconsin</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 04:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</guid>
      <description>Another ski trip. This time just for a day. I loved skiing last time so much that when I heard that another group was heading to Cascade Mountains, I simply couldn&#39;t resist.
We had two guys who had never skied before so we helped them on the bunny hills and moved on to others slopes. Though I&#39;m a newbie I could tell that the snow at the Ski Brule was better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Ski Trip</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 02:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</guid>
      <description>Lobo(Ski Brule)
    Buckhorn Chalet
   Around twenty of us drove up to Ski Brule, Iron River Michigan, on Thursday and stayed at Buckhorn Chalet right in front of the slopes. The slopes looked so beautiful and scary at the same time. I was excited to ski for the first time the very next day.
  With Staff on bunny hills
   When we reached there, there was a free lessons for first timers (should register beforehand).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skiing</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</guid>
      <description>Skiing is fun. As a beginner, it is something you will hate during but love afterward. If you have skied already, you&#39;ll easily dismiss me, but if you have not then you&#39;ll know what I&#39;m talking about. Don&#39;t get me wrong here, if you have never been skiing before and if you have a chance, just pack up and go. It is fun. It is as much fun to ski as it is pain as a beginner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>