<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ski on Praveen Lobo</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/ski/</link><description>Recent content in Ski on Praveen Lobo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 04:53:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/ski/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Skiing on Cascade mountains, Wisconsin</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 04:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</guid><description>&lt;p>Another ski trip. This time just for a day. I loved skiing last time so much that when I heard that another group was heading to Cascade Mountains, I simply couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We had two guys who had never skied before so we helped them on the bunny hills and moved on to others slopes. Though I&amp;rsquo;m a newbie I could tell that the snow at &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/">the Ski Brule&lt;/a> was better. At Cascade it was kind of slippery compared to Ski Brule. May be it was due to the weather, it was mid 30s. Duh!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Ski Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 02:43:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/lobo.jpg"
 alt="Lobo(Ski Brule)">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Lobo(Ski Brule)&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/Buckhorn%20Chalet.jpg"
 alt="Buckhorn Chalet">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>Around twenty of us drove up to Ski Brule, Iron River Michigan, on Thursday and stayed at &lt;strong>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/strong> right in front of the slopes. The slopes looked so beautiful and scary at the same time. I was excited to ski for the first time the very next day.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/on%20the%20bunny.jpg"
 alt="With Staff on bunny hills">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>With Staff on bunny hills&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>When we reached there, there was a free lessons for first timers (should register beforehand). The faculty was nice enough to allow me to join even-though I had not registered. They had first-timers-ski-free offer as well which I missed! Anyway, the faculty was helping the inexperienced on the bunny hills in using the ropes, sliding, stopping, turning. They answered my questions, helped me get up, skied down the slope along with me, helped me tremendously in getting used to the rope (this was so difficult at first, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go more than two feet) and were very cheerful. Now when I think of it, I liked the skiing experience because of their good faculty as well. Thumbs up for them. &amp;#x1f44d;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Skiing</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</guid><description>&lt;p>Skiing is fun. As a beginner, it is something you will hate during but love afterward. If you have skied already, you&amp;rsquo;ll easily dismiss me, but if you have not then you&amp;rsquo;ll know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong here, if you have never been skiing before and if you have a chance, just pack up and go. It is fun. It is as much fun to ski as it is pain as a beginner.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>