<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Friends on Praveen Lobo</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/friends/</link><description>Recent content in Friends on Praveen Lobo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 05:40:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Was My Skydiving All About?</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 05:40:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ever since I posted my skydiving post/video and dedicated it to the people fighting against corruption, some of my friends have been teasing me about it. I did what I wanted to and have no regrets. I have been able to shut them up with just asking if they have the balls to do it before talking smack!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I can take a good tease but the attitude of getting things done quickly and avoiding lines even if it means paying bribe irks me to the core. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind having a healthy discussion, but with some so determined to pay bribe to get things done quickly and wholeheartedly oppose anyone who fights corruption, any discussion is a waste of time and energy. Many of my American friends are optimistic and talk positively (esp. knowing the Gandhi episode), but many of my own countrymen are very very skeptical and pessimistic. If well educated people don&amp;rsquo;t support a cause and act overly smart, what do you think will change? Everything has to start some way and someday, why not make this a starting point for a good future?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Deepavali in Milwaukee</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/deepavali-in-milwaukee-2011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/deepavali-in-milwaukee-2011/</guid><description>&lt;p>My second Deepavali in Milwaukee. Celebrated by visiting temple, doing a small pooja at home and then at a friend’s place. Prepared gulab jamun, had lot of wonderful food at potluck in friend’s place. Concluded it with firecrackers.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My roommates kept American dollars next to Indian rupees on the alter. I wonder what they were praying for. &amp;#x1f61d;&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/46-deepavali/deepavali.jpg"
 alt="Deepavali 2011, Milwaukee">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Deepavali 2011, Milwaukee&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>A 21 Year Old Friendship</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 07:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</guid><description>&lt;p>Krishnamurthy. He is my oldest friend. We were in same class in Bangalore for six years starting 1990 before I had to leave. We were not in touch and had not met more than a handful of times in the last fifteen years. Then when I met him, he was still the same! He had moved to a new place and before I knew it, he was gone from there. I tried to find him but in vain.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 02:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="niagara-new-york-united-states">Niagara, New York, United States&lt;/h4>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/29-niagara/Terrapin%20Point%202.jpg"
 alt="Terrapin Point, Goat Island">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Terrapin Point, Goat Island&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>The next day as planned we drove to Niagara falls. There were a lot of people; I could see a lot of Indians as well. You probably won&amp;rsquo;t believe me but I met my a friend from my college (India) with his friends on Goat Island, I had no clue he was also visiting. Then I met another friend of mine from Bangalore on the Observation Tower! My friends were right when they said be prepared to see the place full of &lt;em>desis&lt;/em>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 04:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="cedar-point-sandusky-ohio-united-states">Cedar Point, Sandusky, Ohio, United States.&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>During the long weekend of September 2010, I visited Cedar Point and Niagara falls along with three other friends. It was an awesome trip. We took a flight from Milwaukee to Cleveland Ohio and rented a car from airport for the entire trip. The plan was to go to Cedar Point one day, visit Niagara next day, and head back the day after.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>First we drove to Cedar Point (Sandusky Ohio) from Marriott (Cleveland Airport Marriott). It was already noon by the time we reached there. It looked a bit scary from outside. All those roller coasters, best in America rankings, and &lt;em>never-before-sat-in-a-roller-coaster&lt;/em> feeling. Once we were inside there were huge lines near all coasters and rides. It was obvious that we would not be able to cover all of it especially because my friend and I wanted to sit at the very front in all rides that we take that day. So, we decided to hit the best of Cedar Point.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Camping At Devil's Lake State Park, Wisconsin</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 07:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</guid><description>&lt;p>On a Friday&amp;rsquo;s evening, eight of us set out to Devil&amp;rsquo;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin in two cars. We reached when it was dark and setup three tents in two camps. The rain god was happy and decided not to play spoilsport; it poured only when we were in the tent.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/23-devils-lake/basecamp.jpg"
 alt="Tents at Devil&amp;#39;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Tents at Devil&amp;rsquo;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>We setup campfire, prepared dinner. Made s&amp;rsquo;more in the campfire for the first time; I had no clue what s&amp;rsquo;more was!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Ski Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 02:43:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/lobo.jpg"
 alt="Lobo(Ski Brule)">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Lobo(Ski Brule)&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/Buckhorn%20Chalet.jpg"
 alt="Buckhorn Chalet">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>Around twenty of us drove up to Ski Brule, Iron River Michigan, on Thursday and stayed at &lt;strong>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/strong> right in front of the slopes. The slopes looked so beautiful and scary at the same time. I was excited to ski for the first time the very next day.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/on%20the%20bunny.jpg"
 alt="With Staff on bunny hills">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>With Staff on bunny hills&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>When we reached there, there was a free lessons for first timers (should register beforehand). The faculty was nice enough to allow me to join even-though I had not registered. They had first-timers-ski-free offer as well which I missed! Anyway, the faculty was helping the inexperienced on the bunny hills in using the ropes, sliding, stopping, turning. They answered my questions, helped me get up, skied down the slope along with me, helped me tremendously in getting used to the rope (this was so difficult at first, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go more than two feet) and were very cheerful. Now when I think of it, I liked the skiing experience because of their good faculty as well. Thumbs up for them. &amp;#x1f44d;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Packers, Team Spirit Day</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 07:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</guid><description>&lt;p>The whole office was green! Some pictures(scaled down) from the team spirit day mentioned in my previous post.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Lobo.jpg"
 alt="Yours truly">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Yours truly&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Lobo_Rahul.jpg"
 alt="Rahul and I">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Rahul and I&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packer_Lobo_Parth.jpg"
 alt="Parth and I">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Parth and I&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Lobo_Rahul2.jpg"
 alt="Rahul and I, again.">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Rahul and I, again.&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Pravin_Shailesh_Bharath.jpg"
 alt="Pravin, Shailesh, and Bharath">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Pravin, Shailesh, and Bharath&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Shailesh_Pravin_Bharath.jpg"
 alt="Shailesh, Pravin, and Bharath">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Shailesh, Pravin, and Bharath&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>The game at Major Goolsby&amp;rsquo;s with a couple of my friends - Shailesh, Myself, Balaji, Bharath, Mada, Ramendra (behind the camera).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Happy New Year</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/happy-new-year-2011/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 08:30:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/happy-new-year-2011/</guid><description>&lt;p>I think, this is the first time I was out on the new year (January 1st 00:00:00 to be precise). Either I used to be at home or with family in the Church at this time every year. Had loads of fun last few moments of 2010 and enjoyed starting of 2011 with friends at Whiskey Bar in Milwaukee.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Not sure why I&amp;rsquo;m blogging about it but hey this is my blog and I&amp;rsquo;ll post whatever I want&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Eat Oatmeal Idiots</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</guid><description>&lt;p>I know, the subject is a bit harsh, but it&amp;rsquo;s well suited for all comments I get from my room-mates about eating oats. Oats is one of the food that I just love. I first started having oatmeal three years ago when I came across many articles on the net. I felt like, it was made for me! Why? It&amp;rsquo;s simple, easy to prepare, healthy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Believe it or not with very little or no exercise I was able to cut down all fat and lose weight just by controlling eating habits. Needless to say one of the main ingredients (and the only one for sometime) being oats!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Halloween 2010 - more pics</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010-more-pics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 01:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010-more-pics/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/10-halloween/pic2.JPG"
 alt="V and Evey">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>V and Evey&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/10-halloween/last.JPG"
 alt="Hey, that&amp;#39;s not!">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Hey, that&amp;rsquo;s not!&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>I was once told that people lose their inhibitions when they are behind the mask. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I agree completely.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Halloween 2010</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 03:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dear blog, as you know, uh oh you don&amp;rsquo;t, do you? I never mentioned about it! I&amp;rsquo;m in US right now. The very fact that I haven&amp;rsquo;t mentioned it till now shows how busy I&amp;rsquo;m here! Naah, not really, that&amp;rsquo;s what I say when I turn lazy and forget about you. I won&amp;rsquo;t promise you that I won&amp;rsquo;t again; I can&amp;rsquo;t keep such promises. Sorry!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anyway, this is kind of new. Different lifestyles. Cultures. New friends. Work environment. Schedules. Meetings. Food. Currency. Everything. To some extent, I&amp;rsquo;m leading a different kind of a life which I don&amp;rsquo;t exactly prefer but don&amp;rsquo;t mind trying for some more time.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cricket: India versus USA</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 04:28:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</guid><description>&lt;p>It was about a month after the softball match between &lt;em>India and USA&lt;/em>, the Americans wanted to try a match of Cricket. Rightly so, Cricket to Americans is like softball to Indians. We did have a match and due to less attendance on USA team, it was played after shuffling the teams.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/09-cricket/Cricket_1.jpg"
 alt="Cricket: India vs USA">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Cricket: India vs USA&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/09-cricket/Cricket_2.jpg"
 alt="Cricket: India vs USA">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Cricket: India vs USA&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/09-cricket/Cricket_3.jpg"
 alt="Cricket: India vs USA">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Cricket: India vs USA&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Weekend In Mangalore</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 15:34:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Update (2018): TMI galore!&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Mangalore. Stirs up a lot of feeling. The first city, other than Bangalore, where I spent more than a year, the city where I lived independently, the city where I gained financial independence, the city where I started watching movies (for real!), the city which has given me a few best friends, the city where I fell in love&amp;hellip; I have so many fond memories of this city that I could go on and on and on. But this post is about my visit to Mangalore last weekend.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>