<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>friends on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/friends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in friends on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 05:40:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Was My Skydiving All About?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 05:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I posted my skydiving post/video and dedicated it to the people fighting against corruption, some of my friends have been teasing me about it. I did what I wanted to and have no regrets. I have been able to shut them up with just asking if they have the balls to do it before talking smack!
I can take a good tease but the attitude of getting things done quickly and avoiding lines even if it means paying bribe irks me to the core.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepavali in Milwaukee</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/deepavali-in-milwaukee-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/deepavali-in-milwaukee-2011/</guid>
      <description>My second Deepavali in Milwaukee. Celebrated by visiting temple, doing a small pooja at home and then at a friend’s place. Prepared gulab jamun, had lot of wonderful food at potluck in friend’s place. Concluded it with firecrackers.
My roommates kept American dollars next to Indian rupees on the alter. I wonder what they were praying for. 😝
  Deepavali 2011, Milwaukee
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A 21 Year Old Friendship</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 07:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</guid>
      <description>Krishnamurthy. He is my oldest friend. We were in same class in Bangalore for six years starting 1990 before I had to leave. We were not in touch and had not met more than a handful of times in the last fifteen years. Then when I met him, he was still the same! He had moved to a new place and before I knew it, he was gone from there. I tried to find him but in vain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 02:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Niagara, New York, United States   Terrapin Point, Goat Island
   The next day as planned we drove to Niagara falls. There were a lot of people; I could see a lot of Indians as well. You probably won&amp;rsquo;t believe me but I met my a friend from my college (India) with his friends on Goat Island, I had no clue he was also visiting. Then I met another friend of mine from Bangalore on the Observation Tower!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 04:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Cedar Point, Sandusky, Ohio, United States. During the long weekend of September 2010, I visited Cedar Point and Niagara falls along with three other friends. It was an awesome trip. We took a flight from Milwaukee to Cleveland Ohio and rented a car from airport for the entire trip. The plan was to go to Cedar Point one day, visit Niagara next day, and head back the day after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping At Devil&#39;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 07:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</guid>
      <description>On a Friday&amp;rsquo;s evening, eight of us set out to Devil&amp;rsquo;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin in two cars. We reached when it was dark and setup three tents in two camps. The rain god was happy and decided not to play spoilsport; it poured only when we were in the tent.
   We setup campfire, prepared dinner. Made s&amp;rsquo;more in the campfire for the first time; I had no clue what s&amp;rsquo;more was!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Ski Trip</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 02:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</guid>
      <description>Lobo(Ski Brule)
    Buckhorn Chalet
   Around twenty of us drove up to Ski Brule, Iron River Michigan, on Thursday and stayed at Buckhorn Chalet right in front of the slopes. The slopes looked so beautiful and scary at the same time. I was excited to ski for the first time the very next day.
  With Staff on bunny hills
   When we reached there, there was a free lessons for first timers (should register beforehand).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packers, Team Spirit Day</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 07:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</guid>
      <description>The whole office was green! Some pictures(scaled down) from the team spirit day mentioned in my previous post.
  Yours truly
    Rahul and I
    Parth and I
    Rahul and I, again.
    Pravin, Shailesh, and Bharath
    Shailesh, Pravin, and Bharath
   The game at Major Goolsby&amp;rsquo;s with a couple of my friends - Shailesh, Myself, Balaji, Bharath, Mada, Ramendra (behind the camera).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/happy-new-year-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 08:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/happy-new-year-2011/</guid>
      <description>I think, this is the first time I was out on the new year (January 1st 00:00:00 to be precise). Either I used to be at home or with family in the Church at this time every year. Had loads of fun last few moments of 2010 and enjoyed starting of 2011 with friends at Whiskey Bar in Milwaukee.
Not sure why I&amp;rsquo;m blogging about it but hey this is my blog and I&amp;rsquo;ll post whatever I want&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eat Oatmeal Idiots</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</guid>
      <description>I know, the subject is a bit harsh, but it&amp;rsquo;s well suited for all comments I get from my room-mates about eating oats. Oats is one of the food that I just love. I first started having oatmeal three years ago when I came across many articles on the net. I felt like, it was made for me! Why? It&amp;rsquo;s simple, easy to prepare, healthy.
Believe it or not with very little or no exercise I was able to cut down all fat and lose weight just by controlling eating habits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2010 - more pics</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010-more-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 01:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010-more-pics/</guid>
      <description>V and Evey
    Hey, that&amp;rsquo;s not!
   I was once told that people lose their inhibitions when they are behind the mask. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I agree completely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2010</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 03:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010/</guid>
      <description>Dear blog, as you know, uh oh you don&amp;rsquo;t, do you? I never mentioned about it! I&amp;rsquo;m in US right now. The very fact that I haven&amp;rsquo;t mentioned it till now shows how busy I&amp;rsquo;m here! Naah, not really, that&amp;rsquo;s what I say when I turn lazy and forget about you. I won&amp;rsquo;t promise you that I won&amp;rsquo;t again; I can&amp;rsquo;t keep such promises. Sorry!
Anyway, this is kind of new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cricket: India versus USA</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 04:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</guid>
      <description>It was about a month after the softball match between India and USA, the Americans wanted to try a match of Cricket. Rightly so, Cricket to Americans is like softball to Indians. We did have a match and due to less attendance on USA team, it was played after shuffling the teams.
  Cricket: India vs USA
    Cricket: India vs USA
    Cricket: India vs USA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weekend In Mangalore</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 15:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</guid>
      <description>Update (2018): TMI galore!
Mangalore. Stirs up a lot of feeling. The first city, other than Bangalore, where I spent more than a year, the city where I lived independently, the city where I gained financial independence, the city where I started watching movies (for real!), the city which has given me a few best friends, the city where I fell in love&amp;hellip; I have so many fond memories of this city that I could go on and on and on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>