<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Travel on Praveen Lobo</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/travel/</link><description>Recent content in Travel on Praveen Lobo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 04:15:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Trip To Pictured Rocks, Michigan</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-trip-to-pictured-rocks-michigan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 04:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-trip-to-pictured-rocks-michigan/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/43-pictured-rocks/En%20route.jpg">
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>Pictured Rocks is a U.S. National Lakeshore on the shore of Lake Superior in the Upper Peninsula of Michigan. It is a beautiful place up north, just google and you won’t disagree. Kayaking in the sea? Wouldn’t it be amazing? We set to find out.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/43-pictured-rocks/Car.jpg"
 alt="Rental Car">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Rental Car&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>&lt;strong>Plan&lt;/strong>: On the September long weekend (Labor day holiday) start from Milwaukee on Saturday, explore Mackinac Island, Pictured Rocks sea kayaking on Sunday, and sightseeing and returning on Monday.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Camping At Big Foot Beach State Park</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-big-foot-beach-state-park-lake-geneva/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 01:36:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-big-foot-beach-state-park-lake-geneva/</guid><description>&lt;p>Another summer, another camping. This time at &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?client=ubuntu&amp;amp;channel=cs&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;q=Big&amp;#43;Foot&amp;#43;State&amp;#43;Park,&amp;#43;Lake&amp;#43;Geneva&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hq=Big&amp;#43;Foot&amp;#43;State&amp;#43;Park,&amp;amp;hnear=0x880584e9f85c4509:0x9eb9a6efc12afe43,Lake&amp;#43;Geneva,&amp;#43;WI&amp;amp;cid=0,0,7166353873496965653&amp;amp;ll=42.574321,-88.438568&amp;amp;spn=0.126411,0.343323&amp;amp;z=11&amp;amp;source=embed">Big Foot Beach State Park, Lake Geneva&lt;/a>. It is located very close to the lake and is right in the city. Four of us camped from Friday evening to Sunday morning with two friends visting Saturday night.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Some pictures from camping at Big Foot beach State Park.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/tent.jpg"
 alt="Tent">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Tent&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/fire.jpg"
 alt="Campfire">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Campfire&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/moonlit%20sky.jpg"
 alt="Sky">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Sky&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/some%20trail.jpg"
 alt="Some Trail">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Some Trail&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/swing.jpg"
 alt="Swing">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Swing&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/soda.jpg"
 alt="Soda Vending Machine!">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Soda Vending Machine!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 02:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="niagara-new-york-united-states">Niagara, New York, United States&lt;/h4>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/29-niagara/Terrapin%20Point%202.jpg"
 alt="Terrapin Point, Goat Island">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Terrapin Point, Goat Island&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>The next day as planned we drove to Niagara falls. There were a lot of people; I could see a lot of Indians as well. You probably won&amp;rsquo;t believe me but I met my a friend from my college (India) with his friends on Goat Island, I had no clue he was also visiting. Then I met another friend of mine from Bangalore on the Observation Tower! My friends were right when they said be prepared to see the place full of &lt;em>desis&lt;/em>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 04:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="cedar-point-sandusky-ohio-united-states">Cedar Point, Sandusky, Ohio, United States.&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>During the long weekend of September 2010, I visited Cedar Point and Niagara falls along with three other friends. It was an awesome trip. We took a flight from Milwaukee to Cleveland Ohio and rented a car from airport for the entire trip. The plan was to go to Cedar Point one day, visit Niagara next day, and head back the day after.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>First we drove to Cedar Point (Sandusky Ohio) from Marriott (Cleveland Airport Marriott). It was already noon by the time we reached there. It looked a bit scary from outside. All those roller coasters, best in America rankings, and &lt;em>never-before-sat-in-a-roller-coaster&lt;/em> feeling. Once we were inside there were huge lines near all coasters and rides. It was obvious that we would not be able to cover all of it especially because my friend and I wanted to sit at the very front in all rides that we take that day. So, we decided to hit the best of Cedar Point.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Camping At Devil's Lake State Park, Wisconsin</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 07:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</guid><description>&lt;p>On a Friday&amp;rsquo;s evening, eight of us set out to Devil&amp;rsquo;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin in two cars. We reached when it was dark and setup three tents in two camps. The rain god was happy and decided not to play spoilsport; it poured only when we were in the tent.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/23-devils-lake/basecamp.jpg"
 alt="Tents at Devil&amp;#39;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Tents at Devil&amp;rsquo;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>We setup campfire, prepared dinner. Made s&amp;rsquo;more in the campfire for the first time; I had no clue what s&amp;rsquo;more was!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Skiing on Cascade mountains, Wisconsin</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 04:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</guid><description>&lt;p>Another ski trip. This time just for a day. I loved skiing last time so much that when I heard that another group was heading to Cascade Mountains, I simply couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We had two guys who had never skied before so we helped them on the bunny hills and moved on to others slopes. Though I&amp;rsquo;m a newbie I could tell that the snow at &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/">the Ski Brule&lt;/a> was better. At Cascade it was kind of slippery compared to Ski Brule. May be it was due to the weather, it was mid 30s. Duh!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Ski Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 02:43:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/lobo.jpg"
 alt="Lobo(Ski Brule)">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Lobo(Ski Brule)&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/Buckhorn%20Chalet.jpg"
 alt="Buckhorn Chalet">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>Around twenty of us drove up to Ski Brule, Iron River Michigan, on Thursday and stayed at &lt;strong>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/strong> right in front of the slopes. The slopes looked so beautiful and scary at the same time. I was excited to ski for the first time the very next day.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/on%20the%20bunny.jpg"
 alt="With Staff on bunny hills">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>With Staff on bunny hills&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>When we reached there, there was a free lessons for first timers (should register beforehand). The faculty was nice enough to allow me to join even-though I had not registered. They had first-timers-ski-free offer as well which I missed! Anyway, the faculty was helping the inexperienced on the bunny hills in using the ropes, sliding, stopping, turning. They answered my questions, helped me get up, skied down the slope along with me, helped me tremendously in getting used to the rope (this was so difficult at first, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go more than two feet) and were very cheerful. Now when I think of it, I liked the skiing experience because of their good faculty as well. Thumbs up for them. &amp;#x1f44d;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Skiing</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</guid><description>&lt;p>Skiing is fun. As a beginner, it is something you will hate during but love afterward. If you have skied already, you&amp;rsquo;ll easily dismiss me, but if you have not then you&amp;rsquo;ll know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong here, if you have never been skiing before and if you have a chance, just pack up and go. It is fun. It is as much fun to ski as it is pain as a beginner.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>From India To USA</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-india-to-usa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-india-to-usa/</guid><description>&lt;p>I can write a detailed travelogue, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to bore you to death! I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m good at writing! Here is the short version! &amp;#x1f603;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A weeks notice was all I got about my first ever business trip. To work at client&amp;rsquo;s location, to deal with client interaction, to deal with the cultural differences, and the list goes on. Though I was prepared for all of it, I was caught off guard with other stuff.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Weekend In Mangalore</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 15:34:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Update (2018): TMI galore!&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Mangalore. Stirs up a lot of feeling. The first city, other than Bangalore, where I spent more than a year, the city where I lived independently, the city where I gained financial independence, the city where I started watching movies (for real!), the city which has given me a few best friends, the city where I fell in love&amp;hellip; I have so many fond memories of this city that I could go on and on and on. But this post is about my visit to Mangalore last weekend.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>