<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>timer on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/timer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in timer on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 20:57:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/timer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript CountUp/CountDown Timer</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countup-countdown-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 20:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countup-countdown-timer/</guid>
      <description>This might be the last one in the JavaScript Counter posts unless I make all-in-one script or a jQuery plugin off of these scripts.
This counter acts as a count down as well as count up timer. As soon as the count down goes to 0 i.e. the future date is hit, the counter turns into a count up timer and keeps going. This counter takes a date to count the time to, an ID to put the timer in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript CountDown Timer</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countdown-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 06:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countdown-timer/</guid>
      <description>This counter takes a date to count the time to, an ID to put the timer in. It is possible to have more than one timer on a page. Demo page.
As soon as the count down goes to 0 i.e. the future date is hit, the counter stops at 0 years 0 months 0 days 00 hours 00 minutes 00 seconds.
Please do leave me a comment. Thanks!
/********************************************************************************************** # MIT License # # Copyright (c) 2011 Praveen Lobo (praveenlobo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Counter</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-counter-count-days-hours-minutes-seconds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 05:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-counter-count-days-hours-minutes-seconds/</guid>
      <description>I keep getting requests and I can&#39;t help but post another JavaScript related counter! As always, in case of any issues/doubts/suggestions, feel free to leave a comment.
JavaScript Counter to Count Days Hours Minutes Seconds - This script is very simple; it takes a date to count the time from/to, an ID to put the timer in. To be very precise, this counter shows the total number of 24 hours intervals between the date-time given and current date-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Javascript Counter</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-counter-count-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 00:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-counter-count-days/</guid>
      <description>John Watt sent me a request asking if I could help with changing the JavaScript CountUp Timer to show only the number of days in a counter. He also wanted to display the days in 3 digits.
I did reply with changes but it had a defect due to a last minute change! So, I wrote a clean script which is the reason for this post. One main improvement here is, the script doesn&#39;t update every second.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript CountUp Timer</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countup-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2010 13:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countup-timer/</guid>
      <description>_Update (2018):_ I have moved the code to [GitHub - JavaScript Counters](https://github.com/lobopraveen/JavaScript-Counters) AS IS.  I was in need of timer to mark an important decision; I did what most of us would do - search on the internet. I found quite a few of them, but I didn&#39;t like any of them. Some of them were unnecessarily complicated; a couple of others weren&#39;t easily understandable; most of them were using approximation (esp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>