<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sports on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sports on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 06:41:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Indians Are The World Champions</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 06:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</guid>
      <description>You know by now. Indians are the world champions! Yeah, say that again, WE ARE THE CHAMPIONS!
Remember &amp;ldquo;More than a billion hearts and one shared dream&amp;rdquo;? That&#39;s what I wrote when the world cup started. That dream has come true! Now more than 50% of Indian population can proudly say they saw their captain lift the world cup at least once in their life. Glory!
Homepage mania: I dedicated the homepage to Green Bay Packers and they won the super bowl; they are the Champions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2011 World Cup</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/</guid>
      <description>My dear fellow Indians and everyone,
Remember 1983 Prudential world cup? Remember Captain Kapil Dev&#39;s greatest catch that dethroned King Viv? No? Neither do I! It&#39;s been 28 years since our captain lifted the cricket world cup. Not just me, nearly 50% of the current Indian population wasn&#39;t even born back then!
More than a billion hearts and one shared dream, to see the men in blue lift the 2011 cricket world cup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Bay Packer on my Homepage</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/green-bay-packer-on-my-homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 07:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/green-bay-packer-on-my-homepage/</guid>
      <description>Hello world,
I dedicated my homepage for Green Bay Packers on 6th February, 2011 and what they got me the same day?! THE SUPER BOWL!
It&#39;s hard not to be a packer fan.
Yours truly,
Newest Packer Fan in town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northwestern Mutual Supports Green Bay Packers</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 05:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</guid>
      <description>Pictures of Northwestern Mutual Insurance company in downtown Milwaukee during NFL 2011 showing support for Green Bay Packers.
Photo courtesy: Sushanth Mohan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packers, Team Spirit Day</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 07:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</guid>
      <description>The whole office was green! Some pictures(scaled down) from the team spirit day mentioned in my previous post.
The game at Major Goolsby&#39;s with a couple of my friends - Shailesh, Myself, Balaji, Bharath, Mada, Ramendra (behind the camera).
Northwestern Mutual building in downtown Milwaukee illuminated to support home team on January 23rd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bears Still Suck!!!</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-bears-still-suck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 03:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-bears-still-suck/</guid>
      <description>Green Bay Packers didn&#39;t disappoint in the playoff; they did just what I hoped for in my previous post, First Winter in Milwaukee. They kicked the Bears ass.
I watched the game at Major Goolsby’s with a couple of my friends. Packers played really well in the first and second quarter with a touchdown in each. Then their game was down and they were struggling just like Chicago Bears (but, the bears still suck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Winter in Milwaukee</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 06:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>Just when I started to laugh at people who were scaring me about the winter, mother nature made sure I shut up. It was a total pain to walk 6 blocks back home from office today! The main problem is the wind. If it isn&#39;t for the wind chill factor, the winter is not much of a problem.
It&#39;s getting freaking cold here in Milwaukee; it&#39;s expected to hit -8°F(-22°C) tomorrow and with the wind and other factors, it&#39;s expected to feel like -27°F(-32°C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cricket: India versus USA</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 04:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</guid>
      <description>It was about a month after the softball match between India and USA, the Americans wanted to try a match of Cricket. Rightly so, Cricket to Americans is like softball to Indians. We did have a match and due to less attendance on USA team, it was played after shuffling the teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hands of God</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hands-of-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 21:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hands-of-god/</guid>
      <description>Uruguay vs. Ghana Quarter final match - 2010 FIFA World Cup
I was sleepy, but somehow this match seemed too good to miss. I had to wash my face with cold water to stay awake. I must tell you, it was WORTH it. Much much more than WORTH it. An exciting match. Last few moments I had my heart in my mouth. I wasn&#39;t supporting any of the teams, but still I feel heartbroken; Ghana should have won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highest Runs In An ODI Match – Sachin Tendulkar</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/highest-runs-in-an-odi-match-sachin-tendulkar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 04:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/highest-runs-in-an-odi-match-sachin-tendulkar/</guid>
      <description>I have come across a lot of comments, communications, posts, and people (even my Dad and Bro) where they mention how they hated a Pakistani cricketer(Saeed Anwar) holding the record for highest ODI runs in a match. I don&#39;t understand! A cricketer is a cricketer, a game is a game, a record is a record, what does it have to do with the citizenship?
What would you(esp. Indians) have called Sachin, if he was a Pakistani?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>