<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>packers on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/packers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in packers on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 03:12:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/packers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m An Indian Green Bay Packer Owner!</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/im-an-indian-green-bay-packer-owner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 03:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/im-an-indian-green-bay-packer-owner/</guid>
      <description>Well, the magic spell is over! Packers won 19 consecutive games before I ever saw them lose. It was rather disappointing to see them lose against Chiefs; it was heartbreaking to see them lose in the very first game of the playoffs. That doesn’t deter me from calling myself a Packer fan.
Oh, wait a minute, I’m not just a fan; I’m a mutual owner of Green Bay Packers! I own a part of NFL’s most mesmerizing team - the Green Bay Packers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Perfect Season - Green Bay Packers</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-perfect-season-green-bay-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 18:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-perfect-season-green-bay-packers/</guid>
      <description>Elle Meissner - The Lions haven’t won a championship since her grandfather was 5 and haven’t won a playoff game since her father was 10, in her lifetime, the Detroit Lions haven’t lost a game. more
 This news reminded me that I haven&#39;t seen a single game that Green Bay Packers lost! The first time I heard of American Football was at the end of 2006 in a session helping people understand the basics of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Game At The Lambeau Field</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-game-at-the-lambeau-field-packers-vs-saints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 01:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-game-at-the-lambeau-field-packers-vs-saints/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned earlier, I was able to get the tickets for the opening game of the season on September 8th, 2011. The world champions take on the New Orleans Saints. We also managed to make some time to visit the hall of fame. One thing I learned during this visit was the super bowl ring is not given just to the players but also to coaches, trainers, executives, personnel, and general staff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit To The Frozen Tundra</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-visit-to-the-frozen-tundra-lambeau-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 01:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-visit-to-the-frozen-tundra-lambeau-field/</guid>
      <description>Lambeau Field
   I have driven around the stadium once while returning from the Door County last fall. This time while returning from a trip to Pictured Rocks, I visited the Lambeau Field a.k.a The Frozen Tundra and took a tour of the stadium. It was just so unbelievable to be there and to learn some history about the Packers. I even got a customized replica jersey and a Packer&#39;s Rubik cube among other things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indians Are The World Champions</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 06:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</guid>
      <description>You know by now. Indians are the world champions! Yeah, say that again, WE ARE THE CHAMPIONS!
Remember &amp;ldquo;More than a billion hearts and one shared dream&amp;rdquo;? That&#39;s what I wrote when the world cup started. That dream has come true! Now more than 50% of Indian population can proudly say they saw their captain lift the world cup at least once in their life. Glory!
Homepage mania: I dedicated the homepage to Green Bay Packers and they won the super bowl; they are the Champions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Bay Packer on my Homepage</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/green-bay-packer-on-my-homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 07:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/green-bay-packer-on-my-homepage/</guid>
      <description>Hello world,
I dedicated my homepage for Green Bay Packers on 6th February, 2011 and what they got me the same day?! THE SUPER BOWL!
It&#39;s hard not to be a packer fan.
  Packer Fans on Super Bowl day
    Packer Fans on Super Bowl day
    Northwestern Mutual Superbowl XLV celebration - Vince Lombardi Ice Trophy
   Yours truly,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northwestern Mutual Supports Green Bay Packers</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 05:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</guid>
      <description>Pictures of Northwestern Mutual Insurance company in downtown Milwaukee during NFL 2011 showing support for Green Bay Packers.
  Northwestern Mutual East Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee
    Northwestern Mutual South Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee
   Photo courtesy: Sushanth Mohan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packers, Team Spirit Day</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 07:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</guid>
      <description>The whole office was green! Some pictures(scaled down) from the team spirit day mentioned in my previous post.
  Yours truly
    Rahul and I
    Parth and I
    Rahul and I, again.
    Pravin, Shailesh, and Bharath
    Shailesh, Pravin, and Bharath
   The game at Major Goolsby&#39;s with a couple of my friends - Shailesh, Myself, Balaji, Bharath, Mada, Ramendra (behind the camera).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bears Still Suck!!!</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-bears-still-suck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 03:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-bears-still-suck/</guid>
      <description>Green Bay Packers didn&#39;t disappoint in the playoff; they did just what I hoped for in my previous post, First Winter in Milwaukee. They kicked the Bears ass.
I watched the game at Major Goolsby’s with a couple of my friends. Packers played really well in the first and second quarter with a touchdown in each. Then their game was down and they were struggling just like Chicago Bears (but, the bears still suck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Winter in Milwaukee</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 06:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>Just when I started to laugh at people who were scaring me about the winter, mother nature made sure I shut up. It was a total pain to walk 6 blocks back home from office today! The main problem is the wind. If it isn&#39;t for the wind chill factor, the winter is not much of a problem.
It&#39;s getting freaking cold here in Milwaukee; it&#39;s expected to hit -8°F(-22°C) tomorrow and with the wind and other factors, it&#39;s expected to feel like -27°F(-32°C).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>