<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bookmark Tool/Manager Using JavaScript And jQuery Autocomplete</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/bookmark-tool-using-javascript-and-jquery-autocomplete/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/bookmark-tool-using-javascript-and-jquery-autocomplete/</guid>
      <description>How do you manage your bookmarks?
 This is a regular question usually from new team members for the past ten years or so. My answer has been the same, &amp;ldquo;I use a tool I wrote.&amp;rdquo; followed by, &amp;ldquo;I will send you the LAN location where I have saved it. You can use it from there or just make a copy of your own.&amp;rdquo;
I remember myself asking that question to others when I first started the job in mid 2000s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Static Site on GitHub - Continuous Integration/Deployment</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hugo-static-site-github-continuous-integration-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hugo-static-site-github-continuous-integration-deployment/</guid>
      <description>After migrating the blog to Hugo and making some custom changes, it was time to develop the CI-CD pipeline. The key objectives for my CI-CD pipeline were
 to be able to build the site locally and to be able to build the site remotely on an integration server  Build Locally More often than not, I use my computer to post stuff on this site. As I already have the site repo and Hugo on my machine, I run the hugo server --buildDrafts while editing the repo with a browser window open on my secondary monitor to monitor the edits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Static Site on GitHub - Customizations</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hugo-static-site-on-github-customizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hugo-static-site-on-github-customizations/</guid>
      <description>While working on migrating this site from WordPress to Hugo, I did tweak somethings to make it work for my liking. I usually keep things simple so that future changes are as painless as possible, however, I decided to go ahead with these changes as it improved maintainability and reverting these changes are very straight forward.
Hugo&amp;rsquo;s default publish directory Hugo generates the static site content in public directory by default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From WordPress to A Static Site Generator</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-wordpress-to-a-static-site-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-wordpress-to-a-static-site-generator/</guid>
      <description>I have been telling myself that I will get back into blogging again and again in vain. I have a bunch of drafts that I have not posted; I keep thinking about posting them and posting my views about current affairs and daily life. For some reason I just can&amp;rsquo;t commit to it. I feel like I have hit this big writer&amp;rsquo;s block and I somehow don&amp;rsquo;t want to get out if it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shell Scripts to Manipulate The File Name Extensions</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/shell-scripts-to-manipulate-the-file-name-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/shell-scripts-to-manipulate-the-file-name-extensions/</guid>
      <description>The latest version of this should be available on GitHub repo. Please report any issues there.
The following snippets show how to change the file name extensions on multiple files on UNIX machines. Other commands like rename and mmv might offer alternatives when they are available on the systems. The scripts below use shell&amp;rsquo;s parameter expansion to operate on multiple files.
 % in below scripts match shortest from the end of the string.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Error Converting The Data Type</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/sql-error-converting-the-data-type/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/sql-error-converting-the-data-type/</guid>
      <description>A team mate of mine approached me asking for help in debugging an issue that has been ongoing for a while. He mentioned that the issue with query he was dealing with was sporadic and doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen in all environments. That sounded interesting. I asked him to pull up a chair so we can go over it together.
The problem was with a query that used to run fine for a long time and started failing a couple of weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Presidential Elections</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/us-presidential-election-2016-trump-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 03:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/us-presidential-election-2016-trump-card/</guid>
      <description>The 2016 US presidential election campaigns are underway, and they are very entertaining! I do not know to the full extent how this entire presidential election works. I doubt if many of the US citizens even understand how this works! So, I spent a couple of hours on this topic and decided to write about it. If you find any inaccuracies, I will be glad to fix it!
US presidential elections are important not just for the Americans but also for the rest of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOLY CRAP!!!</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holy-crap-missing-in-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 20:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holy-crap-missing-in-action/</guid>
      <description>HOLY MOTHER OF SWEET BABY CORN! It has seriously been a long while! 3 years? 4 years? Surprised the blog still exists! LOL! Actually not that much surprised. I pay every year to renew hosting so I know it exists! 😛
The TODO list thing I do. Seriously, it has gotten out of hand! I have unfinished drafts from 2011, 2012, 2013 which are still not posted! I feel embarrassed; at the same time I feel overwhelmed thinking how fast the time flies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Excel To Compare Multiple XMLs</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/using-excel-to-compare-multiple-xmls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/using-excel-to-compare-multiple-xmls/</guid>
      <description>The VBA code from last post explains how two XML strings that are already on the spreadsheet can be compared. This can be extended to add a search functionality to search and bring in the XML before running the comparison.
Search File: To get a matching line from a file, use VBA code as shown here on the gists repo I maintain. Or just use power query as shown below and place the result in the XML cell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Two XMLs In Excel VBA</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/comparing-two-xmls-in-excel-vba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/comparing-two-xmls-in-excel-vba/</guid>
      <description>The easiest way to compare two XML files would be to see if any available tool can do the job. My favorite compare tool to use at work is Beyond Compare - it supports folders as well as files comparison, supports multiple file formats, and has ton of options. For personal use, I prefer meld as it is free and gets the job done.
Although those are wonderful programs, they don&amp;rsquo;t fit every use case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Commas From Values in CSV File</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/remove-commas-from-values-in-csv-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/remove-commas-from-values-in-csv-file/</guid>
      <description>The latest version of this should be available on GitHub repo. Please report any issues there.
CSV files with values that contain commas in them is a pain if the system was built to handle the basic CSV format. This is especially true if the process that has been running for ages fails one day in production and it turns out that the file to process has a value that contains a comma in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Have I Been Up To This Summer?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 17:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>It has been a long time since I blogged regularly. We have a couple of weeks of summer left in 2012 and I don’t want to waste that spending more time on blogging. Lately, I have been feeling like blogging is a winter activity (not saying that I blog regularly in winter). There are a number of topics blog about but no time. I keep adding topics to the todo list and keep deleting when I revisit because it’s either too late or it is making the list too big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ride Lobo Ride - UPAF Ride For The Arts 2012</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/ride-lobo-ride-upaf-ride-for-the-arts-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 16:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/ride-lobo-ride-upaf-ride-for-the-arts-2012/</guid>
      <description>Over quarter of a million participants have taken part in annual United Performing Arts Fund (UPAF) Ride for the Arts since 1981. According to UPAF, which provides financial support to 36 beneficiary groups, the ride helps keep the performing arts scene dynamic and a vital part of the community&amp;rsquo;s culture and that they are among the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest united arts funds in terms of dollars raised and number of donors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Second Bicycle</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-second-bicycle-a-2012-trek-ds-8-3-bicycle-from-wheel-and-sprocket-bike-expo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 03:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-second-bicycle-a-2012-trek-ds-8-3-bicycle-from-wheel-and-sprocket-bike-expo/</guid>
      <description>I used to love bicycles until I started working and moved on to ride motorbikes. Motorbikes were convenient, affordable, and fast. I had bought myself a TVS Suzuki Fiero DS (India&amp;rsquo;s first 150cc bike I think) and I was using it for everyday commute. I had sold my first bicycle and didn&amp;rsquo;t have one to ride. As it happens as one grows up, I had given up on bicycles.
After moving to US, I live very close walk to work and don&amp;rsquo;t need any vehicles for travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Bicycle - An Hercules MTB</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-bicycle-hercules-mtb-bangalore-year-2000/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 01:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-bicycle-hercules-mtb-bangalore-year-2000/</guid>
      <description>As a kid I was jealous of my brother, my cousin, and all my friends (who knew how to ride a bicycle). I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to ride a bike until I was thirteen or fourteen I think. My mom was too scared to allow me to ride a bicycle. I&amp;rsquo;d lie to mom and go trying to ride a bike instead of playing. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember anyone helping me how to ride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m An Indian Green Bay Packer Owner!</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/im-an-indian-green-bay-packer-owner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 03:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/im-an-indian-green-bay-packer-owner/</guid>
      <description>Well, the magic spell is over! Packers won 19 consecutive games before I ever saw them lose. It was rather disappointing to see them lose against Chiefs; it was heartbreaking to see them lose in the very first game of the playoffs. That doesn’t deter me from calling myself a Packer fan.
Oh, wait a minute, I’m not just a fan; I’m a mutual owner of Green Bay Packers! I own a part of NFL’s most mesmerizing team - the Green Bay Packers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Convert JavaScript Local Date to UTC And UTC To Local Date</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/how-to-convert-javascript-local-date-to-utc-and-utc-to-local-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 07:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/how-to-convert-javascript-local-date-to-utc-and-utc-to-local-date/</guid>
      <description>DST is such a pain when it comes to programming. I wish they just get rid of it. It’d be helpful; however, the programmers will still have to deal with the timezones. I was answering questions related to the timers on this website and I keep getting a lot of questions on DST and the timezones. Even though it seems easy, this topic is very confusing. There are lot many sources on the Internet and reading them confuses the hell out of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daylight Saving Time (DST)</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/daylight-saving-time-dst-should-be-a-part-of-our-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 02:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/daylight-saving-time-dst-should-be-a-part-of-our-history/</guid>
      <description>I was having a conversation with a friend of mine who is convinced that the Daylight Saving Time (DST) change is good and makes perfect sense. I, for one, think that the DST is not useful anymore and it could have been avoided altogether. Just imagine if we didn’t have clocks and a way to time. We would have adjusted our lifestyles automatically to adapt to the nature. Instead of adjusting the clock, we should have adjusted the schedules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Google Voice be free in 2012 and beyond?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/will-google-voice-be-free-in-2012-and-beyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/will-google-voice-be-free-in-2012-and-beyond/</guid>
      <description>From the recent notes I made on the Google Voice and how it uses the carrier minutes and data to operate, it should be free in 2012 and beyond.
Why? Currently, Google Voice is not a VOIP service and it uses the carrier minutes and data to operate which means to make or receive calls the subscriber has to pay the carrier. See the image in that post. If Google Voice doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer VOIP service and starts charging for the voice calls, the subscriber will be double charged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Google Voice Use Minutes or Data?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/does-google-voice-use-minutes-or-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 05:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/does-google-voice-use-minutes-or-data/</guid>
      <description>Does Google Voice Use Minutes or Data? Does Google Voice cost money? How does Google Voice calling or texting work? The answer is Yes, Yes, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know.
Update: See this for more info
Google Voice is an awesome idea and piece of software (if you are willing to give away more self information to Google than you already have). It is not a VOIP service like Google Talk; it is a call management service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Was My Skydiving All About?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 05:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I posted my skydiving post/video and dedicated it to the people fighting against corruption, some of my friends have been teasing me about it. I did what I wanted to and have no regrets. I have been able to shut them up with just asking if they have the balls to do it before talking smack!
I can take a good tease but the attitude of getting things done quickly and avoiding lines even if it means paying bribe irks me to the core.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Anonymous Halloween</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/an-anonymous-halloween-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2011 16:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/an-anonymous-halloween-2011/</guid>
      <description>Tombstone and eyeballs cupcakes    It was that time of the year again when the pumpkins are carved, people get costumed, and walk around downtown, of course, showing off. Guess what I did different this time - I carved a pumpkin! The family I was with loves cars so I thought of carving a Mustang (they own one). I made a sketch of it from a picture I had taken of their car, but decided not to do it as it&amp;rsquo;d be difficult and was probably going to take more time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepavali in Milwaukee</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/deepavali-in-milwaukee-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/deepavali-in-milwaukee-2011/</guid>
      <description>My second Deepavali in Milwaukee. Celebrated by visiting temple, doing a small pooja at home and then at a friend’s place. Prepared gulab jamun, had lot of wonderful food at potluck in friend’s place. Concluded it with firecrackers.
My roommates kept American dollars next to Indian rupees on the alter. I wonder what they were praying for. 😝
   Deepavali 2011, Milwaukee    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java: Get Sub List of Elements between two elements (instead of indexes) in a List</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/java-get-sub-list-of-elements-between-two-elements-instead-of-indexes-in-a-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 04:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/java-get-sub-list-of-elements-between-two-elements-instead-of-indexes-in-a-list/</guid>
      <description>Update: moved the code to github
Java List APIs provides a way to get the elements (sub-list) in a List between two indexes using List subList(int fromIndex, int toIndex). However, there is no API to get the elements in a List between two list elements List subList(Object fromElement, Object toElement). The following code is an example to get the elements (sub-list) &amp;ldquo;between two list elements&amp;rdquo;. This works even if the given element doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist in the List - imagine a list of items with different prices and a sub-list of items between price X and price Y when, say, there are no items with price X or Y.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I tried roller blading</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-tried-roller-blading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 05:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-tried-roller-blading/</guid>
      <description>On the Sweetest Day of 2011, I just happened to visit the Incredi-Roll Skate &amp;amp; Laser Tag Family Fun Center (on Oklahoma) for some rollerblade fun. I always wanted to learn rollerblading. A friend of mine forced me to get into it for sometime before giving up on me. But this sweetest day, I gave it a try. It&amp;rsquo;s indoors so there&amp;rsquo;s no danger of getting run over by a truck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Perfect Season - Green Bay Packers</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-perfect-season-green-bay-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 18:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-perfect-season-green-bay-packers/</guid>
      <description>Elle Meissner - The Lions haven’t won a championship since her grandfather was 5 and haven’t won a playoff game since her father was 10, in her lifetime, the Detroit Lions haven’t lost a game. more
 This news reminded me that I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen a single game that Green Bay Packers lost! The first time I heard of American Football was at the end of 2006 in a session helping people understand the basics of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Needs A Genius To Understand The Simplicity</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/it-needs-a-genius-to-understand-the-simplicity-r-i-p-dennis-ritchie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 02:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/it-needs-a-genius-to-understand-the-simplicity-r-i-p-dennis-ritchie/</guid>
      <description>U changed the world; it is because of the people like you we C the world the way it is today. You didn&amp;rsquo;t make billions, but billionaires. You have such an impact not only on those who lived in your lifetime, but also on those who are yet to C the light of the day. Your influence is ubiquitous. The mankind will forever be grateful to you.
R.I.P. Dennis Ritchie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Game At The Lambeau Field</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-game-at-the-lambeau-field-packers-vs-saints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 01:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-game-at-the-lambeau-field-packers-vs-saints/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned earlier, I was able to get the tickets for the opening game of the season on September 8th, 2011. The world champions take on the New Orleans Saints. We also managed to make some time to visit the hall of fame. One thing I learned during this visit was the super bowl ring is not given just to the players but also to coaches, trainers, executives, personnel, and general staff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit To The Frozen Tundra</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-visit-to-the-frozen-tundra-lambeau-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 01:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-visit-to-the-frozen-tundra-lambeau-field/</guid>
      <description>Lambeau Field    I have driven around the stadium once while returning from the Door County last fall. This time while returning from a trip to Pictured Rocks, I visited the Lambeau Field a.k.a The Frozen Tundra and took a tour of the stadium. It was just so unbelievable to be there and to learn some history about the Packers. I even got a customized replica jersey and a Packer&amp;rsquo;s Rubik cube among other things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Trip To Pictured Rocks, Michigan</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-trip-to-pictured-rocks-michigan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 04:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-trip-to-pictured-rocks-michigan/</guid>
      <description>Pictured Rocks is a U.S. National Lakeshore on the shore of Lake Superior in the Upper Peninsula of Michigan. It is a beautiful place up north, just google and you won’t disagree. Kayaking in the sea? Wouldn’t it be amazing? We set to find out.
   Rental Car    Plan: On the September long weekend (Labor day holiday) start from Milwaukee on Saturday, explore Mackinac Island, Pictured Rocks sea kayaking on Sunday, and sightseeing and returning on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do It Now, or You Might Never Get A Chance Again</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/do-it-now-or-you-might-never-get-a-chance-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 05:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/do-it-now-or-you-might-never-get-a-chance-again/</guid>
      <description>Finally on August 20th, 2011, I skydived for the first time, not only unheeding my friends&amp;rsquo; suggestions to go for tandem first and then solo/Accelerated Free Fall (AFF) but also my own fear of jumping into the unknown. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how it will be to fall from 14,000 feet, descending at 120MPH (193KMPH). I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if the instructors will be able to guide me ntil the pull; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if the parachute will open fine or not; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if I would land on Interstate-94 and get dragged down the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story Of My Childhood</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-story-of-my-childhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 04:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-story-of-my-childhood/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend, I had one of my friend come over from Chicago. I hadn&amp;rsquo;t met him in nearly 6-7 years until a couple of days ago when I met him Chicago. We went skydiving, and visited Lake Geneva and had good time together. Meeting him brought back many memories from my childhood and school days and inspired me to write. I think, it&amp;rsquo;s time to share and put them down here before they are completely erased from my already weak memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A 21 Year Old Friendship</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 07:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</guid>
      <description>Krishnamurthy. He is my oldest friend. We were in same class in Bangalore for six years starting 1990 before I had to leave. We were not in touch and had not met more than a handful of times in the last fifteen years. Then when I met him, he was still the same! He had moved to a new place and before I knew it, he was gone from there. I tried to find him but in vain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Paid A Bribe Once</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-paid-a-bribe-once/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 05:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-paid-a-bribe-once/</guid>
      <description>When I was growing up, I used to read the articles in the newspaper about people returning the money/jewelry that somebody else had lost, the auto driver returning thousands of rupees the passengers had left behind. I used to wonder what made them do what they did especially when the person who did it was indeed very poor. Why didn&amp;rsquo;t s/he keep it her/himself, used it to feed his family, made a life out of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Hell Of A Tiring Weekend</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/one-hell-of-a-tiring-weekend-skydive-plan-gone-wrong-and-lake-geneva-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 03:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/one-hell-of-a-tiring-weekend-skydive-plan-gone-wrong-and-lake-geneva-again/</guid>
      <description>If everything went according to the plan, I&amp;rsquo;d have had my first ever free-fall by now. But the mother nature had some other plans. Six friends and I had planned for a skydiving weekend on my room-mate&amp;rsquo;s birthday last Saturday. Two of them had come down from Chicago. The venue was none other than the closest Skydive Midwest. None of us had previous experience and were looking forward to having a great time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A couple of ways to tokenize a delimited String in Java</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-couple-of-ways-to-tokenize-a-delimited-string-in-java/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 03:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-couple-of-ways-to-tokenize-a-delimited-string-in-java/</guid>
      <description>StringTokenizer: It is a legacy class and its use is discouraged in new code. I don&amp;rsquo;t like to use this class even if it weren&amp;rsquo;t a legacy class because it ignores blank tokens. Below code will not output the blank(&amp;ldquo;&amp;rdquo;) between A and In and the last blank token after Me.
StringTokenizer st = new StringTokenizer(&amp;#34;I,Have,A,,In,Me,&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;,&amp;#34;); while (st.hasMoreTokens()) { System.out.println(st.nextToken()); } split method: Javadoc suggests split method of String or the java.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to scroll elements smoothly in JavaScript/jQuery </title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/how-to-scroll-elements-smoothly-in-javascript-jquery-without-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 02:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/how-to-scroll-elements-smoothly-in-javascript-jquery-without-plugins/</guid>
      <description>There are multitude of ways to scroll the page to bring certain elements to view through code. A few of them below. The code given below can be used to scroll any element with an ID on the page. The demo scrolls the page as well as the contents of a DIV and bring an element to view. These methods also use jQuery&amp;rsquo;s animate() method. To best view the code in action click on RESET before clicking on the buttons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comments are beautiful</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/comments-are-beautiful/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 12:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/comments-are-beautiful/</guid>
      <description>Knowing what the hell you are doing is very important and in the world of programming, letting others know what the hell you are doing is just as important.
We, at least some of us, code for a living. We cannot support it forever. We might change profession, move on to a &amp;lsquo;grass is greener&amp;rsquo; place, worst yet we might not exist at all! There will always be another person working on our code, making a living trying to fix the issues (that we thought will never exist), making it better suite the &amp;lsquo;current world&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress: Moving Some Old Posts To A New Blog</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/wordpress-moving-some-old-posts-to-a-new-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 05:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/wordpress-moving-some-old-posts-to-a-new-blog/</guid>
      <description>I recently moved a bunch of blog posts to a new blog installation. This wasn&amp;rsquo;t necessary but just an exercise to learn what it takes to move the posts. It was easy after a lot of reading. Here is a checklist I prepared. Hope it helps someone looking for similar stuff. Comments and suggestions are welcome. Use it at your own risk!
 WordPress: Install WordPress.
 Plugins: Install necessary plugins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Comments Important?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/why-are-comments-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 03:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/why-are-comments-important/</guid>
      <description>Around three months ago, I was shocked looking at some newly added code in one of our applications. It was naked. Not a single line of comment whatsoever!! I asked the person who wrote it to explain the code and it turned out that the code is indeed very cleverly written. I&amp;rsquo;d rate the code as top notch if only it had comments. When I demanded an explanation, it turned out that he thinks commenting is an utterly boring task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping At Big Foot Beach State Park </title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-big-foot-beach-state-park-lake-geneva/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 01:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-big-foot-beach-state-park-lake-geneva/</guid>
      <description>Another summer, another camping. This time at Big Foot Beach State Park, Lake Geneva. It is located very close to the lake and is right in the city. Four of us camped from Friday evening to Sunday morning with two friends visting Saturday night.
Some pictures from camping at Big Foot beach State Park.
   Tent      Campfire      Sky      Some Trail      Swing      Soda Vending Machine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Rules to Excel at Work</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/three-rules-to-excel-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 04:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/three-rules-to-excel-at-work/</guid>
      <description>My day at work had just began, when I overheard a colleague of mine talking about rule number two. He is very senior to me and is dangerously intelligent! I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop myself from asking him what the rule number two was.
&amp;ldquo;Hey, what is rule number two?&amp;rdquo;, I asked.
&amp;ldquo;Well, do you know rule number one?&amp;rdquo;, he questioned.
I replied, &amp;ldquo;Nope&amp;rdquo;, thinking why didn&amp;rsquo;t I ask about rule number one first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML SELECT/Dropdown with JavaScript/jQuery</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/html-select-dropdown-with-javascript-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 03:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/html-select-dropdown-with-javascript-jquery/</guid>
      <description>A list of commonly needed operations on HTML SELECT/Dropdown using JavaScript/jQuery. Let me know if you find it useful or if you have additions/suggestions to improve the list.
JavaScript // get the element var dd = document.getElementById(&amp;#34;dropdown&amp;#34;); // Get the total number of options dd.length; // Get the index of selected option dd.selectedIndex; // get the value of selected option dd.options[dd.selectedIndex].value; // Get the selected option/text dd.options[dd.selectedIndex].text; // Reset the dropdoown option; select first option dd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O_ops: You have no null items</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-you-have-no-null-items-google-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 13:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-you-have-no-null-items-google-reader/</guid>
      <description>I was browsing through my RSS subscriptions on Google Reader when it confirmed that I have no null items.
   Google Reader - null items    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penny Auction Sites Auto Bidding Script (Sniper)</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites-auto-bidding-script-sniper-how-to-building-and-using-the-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 23:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites-auto-bidding-script-sniper-how-to-building-and-using-the-script/</guid>
      <description>Part I and II of this post series can be found here and here respectively.
5. Build the script: Assume that the HTML skeleton given in previous post is indeed the code and when the bid ends the timer gets a class called BIDEND. Finally, say the code used by the site to place a bid is PennyAuction.placeBid(itemCode);. With this information build a script.
// Get the codes from the user // Note : If it&amp;#39;s integer then parseInt method can be used around the prompt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penny Auction Sites Auto Bidding Script (Sniper)</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites-auto-bidding-script-sniper-how-to-requirements-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 18:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites-auto-bidding-script-sniper-how-to-requirements-preparation/</guid>
      <description>Part I of this post series can be found here.
3. Requirements for the script:  The script shall have a lower limit to start bidding i.e. the script should not start bidding if the actual price in the bid hasn&amp;rsquo;t crossed a set limit.
 The script shall have an upper limit to bidding i.e. it shall stop bidding if the bid price crosses certain limit.
 The script shall bid a fixed number of times i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>34th Roots &amp; Wings Annual Run/Walk 2011</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/34th-roots-wings-annual-runwalk-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 05:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/34th-roots-wings-annual-runwalk-2011/</guid>
      <description>Facebook status on July 24 at 12:40am
 1750 to beat.
 Facebook status on July 24 at 9:57am
 1753 seconds to finish; just 3 seconds dammit.
 Says it all, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
   Roots &amp;amp; Wings T-Shirt    It was the 34th Roots &amp;amp; Wings Annual Run/Walk 2011 (in Milwaukee marks the beginning of the Northwestern Mutual&amp;rsquo;s Annual Meeting of the Association of Network Representatives) and there I was a good 5 minutes late at the start line!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penny Auction Sites Auto Bidding Script (Bid Sniper)</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites-auto-bidding-script-bid-sniper-how-to-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 04:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites-auto-bidding-script-bid-sniper-how-to-introduction/</guid>
      <description>I wrote a prologue to penny auction sites beginning of this year, but never posted the bot script I promised I would! I didn&amp;rsquo;t because I didn&amp;rsquo;t want others to lose money, but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t one use his own judgment before using any advice found on the Internet? Before anything else I would like to warn you - use the information found here at your own risk. I shall not be held liable for any damage - monetary or otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather comparison</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/weather-comparison-bangalore-vs-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 19:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/weather-comparison-bangalore-vs-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>You know by now, I&amp;rsquo;m a bit concerned about this weather. While checking the weather forecast, I came up with this idea of comparing the weather between Bangalore and Milwaukee. Just for giggles.
The below graphs are drawn with the data available freely on the net(weather.com, wikipedia and wunderground.com). I believe they should be fairly accurate.
   Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°F)      Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°C)    Check the interactive graph on weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doesn&#39;t this weather remind you of India?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/doesnt-this-weather-remind-you-of-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 23:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/doesnt-this-weather-remind-you-of-india/</guid>
      <description>The weather has been truly devastating this summer (Milwaukee 2011). National Weather Service issued heat advisory; many sources reminding the deadly heat from 1995 and 1988 which took a lot of lives! The weather forecasts, news-sites, and other sources of information on the internet are terrifying.
Rewind to 2010 I landed exactly one year ago in Milwaukee. The weather was not bad. It compared to the weather I was used to in Bangalore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm The Bastille 2011 - Milwaukee</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/storm-the-bastille-2011-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 05:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/storm-the-bastille-2011-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>The Bastille, the medieval fortress and prison in Paris, was stormed by the demonstrators to acquire the ammunition on 14 July 1789. This day marks the start of the French Revolution and is celebrated as a national holiday in France. The same is celebrated in across the world. One such place is Milwaukee. Yes, the place I live now!
 Bastille Days is North America&amp;rsquo;s largest outdoor French themed festival held in downtown Milwaukee in Cathedral Square Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lost Track</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-lost-track-on-the-streets-of-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 05:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-lost-track-on-the-streets-of-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m one of those lazy ones when it comes to gym or jogging. I don&amp;rsquo;t even remember when I jogged last. Gym has been on and off with a total I can count with my fingers of one hand. After all it&amp;rsquo;s for those who want to be fit; not for those who are already fit. 😉
Anyhow, I started practicing for a 5K run scheduled for June 24th Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O_ops: Better Logging To Solve Problems</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-better-logging-to-solve-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 03:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-better-logging-to-solve-problems/</guid>
      <description>Logging helps in pinpointing the code block that threw an error. Only if they are used correctly. During once such failure, a guy noticed that a script lacked logging and ever promptly promoted the updated script with better logging. A part of the script is shown below.
Script before: 1&amp;gt;&amp;gt;${LOG} 2&amp;gt;&amp;gt;${ERRLOG} ${BINPATH}/${PROGRAMNAME} if [ $? -ne 0 ]; then print &amp;#34;ERROR: Something failed&amp;#34; exit 101 fi
Script after:
1&amp;gt;&amp;gt;${LOG} 2&amp;gt;&amp;gt;${ERRLOG} ${BINPATH}/${PROGRAMNAME} echo &amp;#34;Program completed successfully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I choose to go against using WordPress Multisite?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/why-i-choose-to-go-against-using-wordpress-multisite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 07:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/why-i-choose-to-go-against-using-wordpress-multisite/</guid>
      <description>When you start out with the WordPress, it&amp;rsquo;s common to assume that each blog needs a separate WordPress installation. But there&amp;rsquo;s a simpler way. WordPress Multisite installation. This lets one have different blogs with just one installation of WordPress. But, why did I choose not to use it?
Advantges and Disadvantages of WordPress Multisite Advantages:  The multisite blogs have all features of a regular blog with just one installation i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abused</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/abused/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 05:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/abused/</guid>
      <description>Abused    From archives. Not my original imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript CountUp/CountDown Timer</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countup-countdown-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 20:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countup-countdown-timer/</guid>
      <description>This might be the last one in the JavaScript Counter posts unless I make all-in-one script or a jQuery plugin off of these scripts.
This counter acts as a count down as well as count up timer. As soon as the count down goes to 0 i.e. the future date is hit, the counter turns into a count up timer and keeps going. This counter takes a date to count the time to, an ID to put the timer in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript CountDown Timer</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countdown-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 06:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countdown-timer/</guid>
      <description>This counter takes a date to count the time to, an ID to put the timer in. It is possible to have more than one timer on a page. Demo page.
As soon as the count down goes to 0 i.e. the future date is hit, the counter stops at 0 years 0 months 0 days 00 hours 00 minutes 00 seconds.
Please do leave me a comment. Thanks!
/********************************************************************************************** # MIT License # # Copyright (c) 2011 Praveen Lobo (praveenlobo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Counter</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-counter-count-days-hours-minutes-seconds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 05:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-counter-count-days-hours-minutes-seconds/</guid>
      <description>I keep getting requests and I can&amp;rsquo;t help but post another JavaScript related counter! As always, in case of any issues/doubts/suggestions, feel free to leave a comment.
JavaScript Counter to Count Days Hours Minutes Seconds - This script is very simple; it takes a date to count the time from/to, an ID to put the timer in. To be very precise, this counter shows the total number of 24 hours intervals between the date-time given and current date-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>H1B Interview Questions</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/h1b-interview-questions-chennai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 04:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/h1b-interview-questions-chennai/</guid>
      <description>I had an H1B interview more than an year ago and written two blog posts about my travel to and from Bangalore and stay in Chennai (here and here). Surprisingly, even today &amp;ldquo;h1b&amp;rdquo; is one of the keywords getting highest number of visitors to my site (per Google Analytics). Most of them looking for interview questions. Recently I found a list I had prepared of probable questions the interviewer may ask.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jQuery v1.6 Checkbox issue</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/jquery-v1-6-checkbox-issue-attr-vs-prop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 06:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/jquery-v1-6-checkbox-issue-attr-vs-prop/</guid>
      <description>I have been visiting Stackoverflow a lot recently. This is a cool forum where you not only get your questions answered but also learn. Learn a lot, in fact. I always enjoy learning from others&amp;rsquo; experience and mistakes; it&amp;rsquo;s dirty but it is also very easy and fast. This is exactly what Stackoverflow is providing me; an opportunity to learn from others&amp;rsquo; knowledge. I&amp;rsquo;m also having fun with their reputation points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Javascript Counter</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-counter-count-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 00:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-counter-count-days/</guid>
      <description>John Watt sent me a request asking if I could help with changing the JavaScript CountUp Timer to show only the number of days in a counter. He also wanted to display the days in 3 digits.
I did reply with changes but it had a defect due to a last minute change! So, I wrote a clean script which is the reason for this post. One main improvement here is, the script doesn&amp;rsquo;t update every second.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Small Gift Box For Me, Pain In The Neck For Most</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-small-gift-box-for-me-pain-in-the-neck-for-most/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-small-gift-box-for-me-pain-in-the-neck-for-most/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I really don&amp;rsquo;t mean most by &amp;ldquo;most&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s just the most I encountered here. The other day I had to send some gifts through one of my friend who was travelling in next couple of hours. The idiot that I am, I had forgotten to buy the gift boxes! So, I decided to make them myself. I had just about everything it takes - some cardboard boxes, gift wrap, glue, a pair of scissors, and mighty interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 02:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Niagara, New York, United States    Terrapin Point, Goat Island    The next day as planned we drove to Niagara falls. There were a lot of people; I could see a lot of Indians as well. You probably won&amp;rsquo;t believe me but I met my a friend from my college (India) with his friends on Goat Island, I had no clue he was also visiting. Then I met another friend of mine from Bangalore on the Observation Tower!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 04:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Cedar Point, Sandusky, Ohio, United States. During the long weekend of September 2010, I visited Cedar Point and Niagara falls along with three other friends. It was an awesome trip. We took a flight from Milwaukee to Cleveland Ohio and rented a car from airport for the entire trip. The plan was to go to Cedar Point one day, visit Niagara next day, and head back the day after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Remove The /blog/ slug From The Permalinks(URL) Without A Plugin</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/how-to-remove-the-blog-slug-from-the-permalinksurl-in-wordpress-multisite-installation-without-a-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 06:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/how-to-remove-the-blog-slug-from-the-permalinksurl-in-wordpress-multisite-installation-without-a-plugin/</guid>
      <description>What is a blog slug? If you have no clue, this post isn&amp;rsquo;t for you and if you want to know what it is, it is an ugly looking additional &amp;ldquo;/blog/&amp;rdquo; in the permalinks (URLs) in your website that comes free with the multisite feature in WordPress. Why ugly? Because it comes uninvited, it&amp;rsquo;s there and most probably you don&amp;rsquo;t want it.
How do you remove the additional &amp;ldquo;blog&amp;rdquo; in the URL of your posts?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Personal and Technical Blogs Separate</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/keeping-personal-and-technical-blogs-separate-contd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 06:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/keeping-personal-and-technical-blogs-separate-contd/</guid>
      <description>Continued from here&amp;hellip;
Advantages/Disadvantages: Advantages of multiple blogs include monetization, ease of finding advertisers, reaching right audience, and building a resource of articles all in the same niche. Disadvantages? Unless you are an expert you will run out of good articles, might have to hire writers. Multiple blogs needs more time in terms of maintenance, updates etc. It needs more resources which cost money.
You will have enough time on your hand with a single blog and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about all blogs that miss your constant love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multisite WordPress Installation On Sibling Directories Of An Existing Single Installation</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/multisite-wordpress-installation-on-sibling-directories-of-an-existing-single-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 05:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/multisite-wordpress-installation-on-sibling-directories-of-an-existing-single-installation/</guid>
      <description>Is it possible to create a blog in a sibling directory of an already installed WordPress directory? If yes, how to? If not, can it be done on a fresh installation? 1. Existing Installation: Assume that the domain is praveenlobo.com and there is an existing WordPress installation in /blog directory (so, praveenlobo.com/blog is a WordPress blog and the root directory at praveenlobo.com is free). Now, is it possible to create a networked site or blog at praveenlobo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Blue/Light Blue Maps of India</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/dark-blue-light-blue-maps-of-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 05:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/dark-blue-light-blue-maps-of-india/</guid>
      <description>These are the India maps I created* when designing my homepage for the grand 2011 Cricket World Cup.
I had a tough time searching for a blue map of India online and ended up creating them myself. With this post they are released online; you are free to use them as you may wish. However, a link to this blog is really appreciated (which I&amp;rsquo;m sure none of you are going to do!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Clipper Self Haircut</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-time-clipper-self-haircut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 06:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-time-clipper-self-haircut/</guid>
      <description>[Dated 12/12/2010; Posted 5/2/2011 due to photos.]
If you think this is a &amp;ldquo;own haircut how to&amp;rdquo;, let me tell you, you&amp;rsquo;ll be disappointed because it is not. However, you can read further to find out my tale with giving myself a haircut for the first time.
When I was kid, I had this dream, albeit shot-lived, of becoming an hairstylist. But then I went to college trying to become an engineer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pencil Sketch</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/pencil-sketch-sachin-tendulkar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 06:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/pencil-sketch-sachin-tendulkar/</guid>
      <description>A pencil sketch of the greatest batsman to ever play the game of Cricket - Sachin Tendulkar. Sketched more than half a decade ago. Does it look like Sachin?
   Sachin Tendulkar      Sachin Tendulkar (scanned and GIMP&amp;#39;d)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Personal and Technical Blogs Separate</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/keeping-personal-and-technical-blogs-separate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 04:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/keeping-personal-and-technical-blogs-separate/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I&amp;rsquo;m no expert in blogging. I do not have much knowledge about the Wordpress framework either. The following post is based on my previous couple of hours of reading on multisite blogging. Feel free to enlighten me in the comment section.
Why? If you are starting/have started blogging as a hobby, at first it may seem that having one blog and blogging everything in it is a good idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSS Feed URL Changed</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/rss-feed-url-changed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 06:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/rss-feed-url-changed/</guid>
      <description>Dear readers,
Though there are only a few of you and I&amp;rsquo;m very sure you are very capable of finding it out yourselves, I think I must save your time and tell you that I&amp;rsquo;m moving my RSS Feed address.
The idea is simple:
 I post this post and then
 change my RSS feed address.
  So that, assuming you miss this post, in case you wonder why you are not finding any new unread items in Lobo&amp;rsquo;s blog feed, this is the post you find on the old feed and you know the answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strike Out Corruption In India</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/strike-out-corruption-in-india-support-jan-lokpal-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 07:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/strike-out-corruption-in-india-support-jan-lokpal-bill/</guid>
      <description>CORRUPTION IN INDIA
Will Jan Lokpal bill solve the issue? I don&amp;rsquo;t know for sure, but it will definitely set us on the right path by giving more power to those who matter. It&amp;rsquo;s heartening to see India united to fight against the corruption. If an old man [Anna Hazare] can do so much, why can&amp;rsquo;t the youth do more? If you can, PLEASE SHOW YOUR SUPPORT in any way possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indians Are The World Champions</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 06:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</guid>
      <description>You know by now. Indians are the world champions! Yeah, say that again, WE ARE THE CHAMPIONS!
Remember &amp;ldquo;More than a billion hearts and one shared dream&amp;rdquo;? That&amp;rsquo;s what I wrote when the world cup started. That dream has come true! Now more than 50% of Indian population can proudly say they saw their captain lift the world cup at least once in their life. Glory!
Homepage mania: I dedicated the homepage to Green Bay Packers and they won the super bowl; they are the Champions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O_ops: Facebook Image Compression Sucks!</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-facebook-image-compression-sucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 03:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-facebook-image-compression-sucks/</guid>
      <description>Facebook [profile picture] image compression not only sucks big time, but it is also stupid. I don&amp;rsquo;t use Facebook as an image storage service, neither do I care about the EXIF data that they strip. I&amp;rsquo;m also okay with their approach to compress each and every image(?), but compressing an image which results in an image size bigger than the originally uploaded image? I think it fits in my O_ops series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O_ops: Never Return null For A Collection in Java</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-never-return-null-for-a-collection-in-java/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 06:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-never-return-null-for-a-collection-in-java/</guid>
      <description>I was enjoying a small break between the meetings when my a co-worker asked me to help her out with some Java error in the code she was working on. She was giving me walk-through of the code and I small piece of code caught my attention. Apparently, the coder knew not to return null when returning a collection.
/* Check if the list is null \*/ if(matchingCountryList != null) { return matchingCountryList; } else { return null; } Of course, it was not her code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camping At Devil&#39;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 07:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</guid>
      <description>On a Friday&amp;rsquo;s evening, eight of us set out to Devil&amp;rsquo;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin in two cars. We reached when it was dark and setup three tents in two camps. The rain god was happy and decided not to play spoilsport; it poured only when we were in the tent.
   We setup campfire, prepared dinner. Made s&amp;rsquo;more in the campfire for the first time; I had no clue what s&amp;rsquo;more was!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Year That Was - 2010</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-year-that-was-2010-excerpts-from-the-unborn-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 07:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-year-that-was-2010-excerpts-from-the-unborn-posts/</guid>
      <description>Year 2010 was a totally different and a very special one for me. It all started in late 2009; from someone who used to talk so less and hardly socialize to wherever I am right now was quite a journey. I had a jolly good time and I wish it is one of the many years to come.
2010 had some downs, but I hardly remember them. The good ones are so many that I don&amp;rsquo;t have time to recall the bad ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way To Solve Rubik&#39;s Cube </title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/easiest-way-to-solve-rubiks-cube-without-cheating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 07:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/easiest-way-to-solve-rubiks-cube-without-cheating/</guid>
      <description>The following tutorials/videos helped me a lot in learning to solve the 3x3 Rubik&amp;rsquo;s Cube). I think these are the easiest ways to solve the rubik&amp;rsquo;s cube and hope you find it helpful too. You may find that the technique used is the same, just the explanation differs in most of the cases. Second and third videos take different approaches to solve third layer. Latter is easier and has less number of steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skiing on Cascade mountains, Wisconsin</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 04:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</guid>
      <description>Another ski trip. This time just for a day. I loved skiing last time so much that when I heard that another group was heading to Cascade Mountains, I simply couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist.
We had two guys who had never skied before so we helped them on the bunny hills and moved on to others slopes. Though I&amp;rsquo;m a newbie I could tell that the snow at the Ski Brule was better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing Chocolate Brownie</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/preparing-chocolate-brownie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 23:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/preparing-chocolate-brownie/</guid>
      <description>This is Sunday afternoon, I&amp;rsquo;m bored and I&amp;rsquo;m planning to prepare Chocolate Brownies. I have never prepared it before and looking at the instructions on the pack, I must say it is not big deal at all. All you need is, well, Chocolate Brownie mix, some eggs and vegetable oil. I&amp;rsquo;m off.
PS: Okay, I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything to blog about. Big deal. 😝
   Brownies in the tray      Brownies      More Brownies      Some more Brownies    Brownies were pretty good; they were a little crispy whereas I wanted them to be soft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Ski Trip</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 02:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</guid>
      <description>Lobo(Ski Brule)      Buckhorn Chalet    Around twenty of us drove up to Ski Brule, Iron River Michigan, on Thursday and stayed at Buckhorn Chalet right in front of the slopes. The slopes looked so beautiful and scary at the same time. I was excited to ski for the first time the very next day.
   With Staff on bunny hills    When we reached there, there was a free lessons for first timers (should register beforehand).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skiing</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</guid>
      <description>Skiing is fun. As a beginner, it is something you will hate during but love afterward. If you have skied already, you&amp;rsquo;ll easily dismiss me, but if you have not then you&amp;rsquo;ll know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong here, if you have never been skiing before and if you have a chance, just pack up and go. It is fun. It is as much fun to ski as it is pain as a beginner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2011 World Cup</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/</guid>
      <description>My dear fellow Indians and everyone,
Remember 1983 Prudential world cup? Remember Captain Kapil Dev&amp;rsquo;s greatest catch that dethroned King Viv? No? Neither do I! It&amp;rsquo;s been 28 years since our captain lifted the cricket world cup. Not just me, nearly 50% of the current Indian population wasn&amp;rsquo;t even born back then!
More than a billion hearts and one shared dream, to see the men in blue lift the 2011 cricket world cup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Bay Packer on my Homepage</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/green-bay-packer-on-my-homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 07:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/green-bay-packer-on-my-homepage/</guid>
      <description>Hello world,
I dedicated my homepage for Green Bay Packers on 6th February, 2011 and what they got me the same day?! THE SUPER BOWL!
It&amp;rsquo;s hard not to be a packer fan.
   Packer Fans on Super Bowl day      Packer Fans on Super Bowl day      Northwestern Mutual Superbowl XLV celebration - Vince Lombardi Ice Trophy    Yours truly,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northwestern Mutual Supports Green Bay Packers</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 05:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</guid>
      <description>Pictures of Northwestern Mutual Insurance company in downtown Milwaukee during NFL 2011 showing support for Green Bay Packers.
   Northwestern Mutual East Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee      Northwestern Mutual South Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee    Photo courtesy: Sushanth Mohan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O_ops: Re-try again</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-re-try-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-re-try-again/</guid>
      <description>You can&amp;#39;t attempt more than 5 times, please re-try again!    The best part is that once this message comes, the only way to succeed is to call the service center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packers, Team Spirit Day</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 07:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</guid>
      <description>The whole office was green! Some pictures(scaled down) from the team spirit day mentioned in my previous post.
   Yours truly      Rahul and I      Parth and I      Rahul and I, again.      Pravin, Shailesh, and Bharath      Shailesh, Pravin, and Bharath    The game at Major Goolsby&amp;rsquo;s with a couple of my friends - Shailesh, Myself, Balaji, Bharath, Mada, Ramendra (behind the camera).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bears Still Suck!!!</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-bears-still-suck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 03:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-bears-still-suck/</guid>
      <description>Green Bay Packers didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint in the playoff; they did just what I hoped for in my previous post, First Winter in Milwaukee. They kicked the Bears ass.
I watched the game at Major Goolsby’s with a couple of my friends. Packers played really well in the first and second quarter with a touchdown in each. Then their game was down and they were struggling just like Chicago Bears (but, the bears still suck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Winter in Milwaukee</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 06:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>Just when I started to laugh at people who were scaring me about the winter, mother nature made sure I shut up. It was a total pain to walk 6 blocks back home from office today! The main problem is the wind. If it isn&amp;rsquo;t for the wind chill factor, the winter is not much of a problem.
It&amp;rsquo;s getting freaking cold here in Milwaukee; it&amp;rsquo;s expected to hit -8°F(-22°C) tomorrow and with the wind and other factors, it&amp;rsquo;s expected to feel like -27°F(-32°C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O_ops: It&#39;s Christmas Time</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-its-christmas-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-its-christmas-time/</guid>
      <description>I had been wondering for a last couple of days if I should start a O_ops series to just list downs things that are O_ops. Then I get this email and here I start!
It was Christmas time and I got an unusual wish from a sweetheart friend of mine.
 From: SS
Sent: Friday, December 24, 2010 5:37 PM
To: Lobo
Subject: Its Christmas time :)
Hey Lobo Marry Christmas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working on The Blog</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/working-on-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 09:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/working-on-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>This is a perfect example for a seemingly easy task taking up so much of one&amp;rsquo;s time. I have been busy working on this blog for a last couple of days. I spent so much time and yet there are so many things to do!
Here is what I have done so far:
 Updated feed through FeedBurner: this was already present, I updated some settings.
 Added Google AdSense: there comes a time in everyone&amp;rsquo;s life when they turn greedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RELATIVE Performance Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/relative-performance-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 23:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/relative-performance-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>if( parseInt(&amp;#34;1&amp;#34;) === parseInt(&amp;#34;1+&amp;#34;) ){ alert(&amp;#34;Depends on &amp;#39;the context&amp;#39; and is controlled by external factors!&amp;#34;); } else { alert(&amp;#34;Loser!&amp;#34;); } alert(&amp;#34;Think again!&amp;#34;);  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penny Auction Sites</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 21:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites/</guid>
      <description>Okay, you must have landed here through some search engine while trying to figure out a way to make a fortune by spending pennies. Those penny auction sites are amazing, aren&amp;rsquo;t they? The concept is so clear and it almost sounds like anyone can get one of those shiny new iPads, Macs, Nikkon D90, or Canon EOS 7D on auction just for a few pennies.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t got a clue about it, I urge you to read about them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/happy-new-year-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 08:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/happy-new-year-2011/</guid>
      <description>I think, this is the first time I was out on the new year (January 1st 00:00:00 to be precise). Either I used to be at home or with family in the Church at this time every year. Had loads of fun last few moments of 2010 and enjoyed starting of 2011 with friends at Whiskey Bar in Milwaukee.
Not sure why I&amp;rsquo;m blogging about it but hey this is my blog and I&amp;rsquo;ll post whatever I want&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Gift 2010</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holiday-gift-2010-organ-donor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 07:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holiday-gift-2010-organ-donor/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any problem communicating it to Mom. She knew it since I was 10 years old or so. I had told her about this wish and so did she. We both want not just organs but entire body to be donated when we pass away.
This is a picture of an eye donation card I signed nearly 15 years ago! (I must have been 10 years old or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Change</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/password-change-identifying-the-weakest-link-in-the-chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 08:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/password-change-identifying-the-weakest-link-in-the-chain/</guid>
      <description>Last evening, I changed my passwords on all accounts on all websites that I frequent. Just curious to know how many did the same. Hopefully someone will come up with the stats soon.
I always use different passwords on different sites. All of them are at least 10+ character long with minimum one capital, special character, and number in it. Curious to know what my friends do, I brought up this topic briefly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2010 - A Long Weekend</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/thanksgiving-2010-a-long-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 01:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/thanksgiving-2010-a-long-weekend/</guid>
      <description>A long weekend (four days) - many of my friends are on trips visiting places. I&amp;rsquo;m sitting here writing this post! I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go due to work. I had to work for a couple of hours exactly in the middle of the four days so I stayed back. It sure doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel good but not as bad as I imagined it to be. Almost 3/4th of the long weekend has gone by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eat Oatmeal Idiots</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</guid>
      <description>I know, the subject is a bit harsh, but it&amp;rsquo;s well suited for all comments I get from my room-mates about eating oats. Oats is one of the food that I just love. I first started having oatmeal three years ago when I came across many articles on the net. I felt like, it was made for me! Why? It&amp;rsquo;s simple, easy to prepare, healthy.
Believe it or not with very little or no exercise I was able to cut down all fat and lose weight just by controlling eating habits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walk of Life</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/walk-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 16:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/walk-of-life/</guid>
      <description>This morning on my way to office I saw an old couple walking across the street. The gentleman was walking at a-couple-inches-a-step pace and the lady, it seemed like, was moving only an inch with every single step. They were crossing a relatively free street and he was holding her hands and leading her. They crossed the street and then turned left to cross another one. A few cars stopped in front of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Culinary Skills - III</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 05:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-iii/</guid>
      <description>Another one from the old drafts. Only pictures this time. :-)
   Step 1      Step 2      Step 3      Step 4      Step 5    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autosys and Unix Permission</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/autosys-and-unix-permission-solved/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 04:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/autosys-and-unix-permission-solved/</guid>
      <description>Original post with the answer at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2010 - more pics</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010-more-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 01:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010-more-pics/</guid>
      <description>V and Evey      Hey, that&amp;#39;s not!    I was once told that people lose their inhibitions when they are behind the mask. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I agree completely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2010</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 03:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010/</guid>
      <description>Dear blog, as you know, uh oh you don&amp;rsquo;t, do you? I never mentioned about it! I&amp;rsquo;m in US right now. The very fact that I haven&amp;rsquo;t mentioned it till now shows how busy I&amp;rsquo;m here! Naah, not really, that&amp;rsquo;s what I say when I turn lazy and forget about you. I won&amp;rsquo;t promise you that I won&amp;rsquo;t again; I can&amp;rsquo;t keep such promises. Sorry!
Anyway, this is kind of new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Culinary Skills - II</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2010 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-ii/</guid>
      <description>This was in draft mode for over 5 months now! There is something with me and updating this blog. There are a couple of more drafts. I plan to post all of them in next two weeks.
If I&amp;rsquo;m not following the recipes which I read somewhere, I will keep it very simple. First I check what are the items I can use, then etch a plan, pick the items, and cook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cricket: India versus USA</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 04:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</guid>
      <description>It was about a month after the softball match between India and USA, the Americans wanted to try a match of Cricket. Rightly so, Cricket to Americans is like softball to Indians. We did have a match and due to less attendance on USA team, it was played after shuffling the teams.
   Cricket: India vs USA      Cricket: India vs USA      Cricket: India vs USA      Cricket: India vs USA    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From India To USA</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-india-to-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-india-to-usa/</guid>
      <description>I can write a detailed travelogue, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to bore you to death! I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m good at writing! Here is the short version! 😃
A weeks notice was all I got about my first ever business trip. To work at client&amp;rsquo;s location, to deal with client interaction, to deal with the cultural differences, and the list goes on. Though I was prepared for all of it, I was caught off guard with other stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Day at the Dance Class</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/last-day-at-the-dance-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 06:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/last-day-at-the-dance-class/</guid>
      <description>A little sadness has taken over me. Today was my last day at Dance Verve. Remember this last paragraph? A week after that I joined Dance Verve at BTM Check Post.
I remember the very first day - I entered the class when Taj Khan (we call him sir) was not yet in. I talked to two guys (now I know them - Pavan and Manas) and sir arrived in about 15 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hands of God</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hands-of-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 21:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hands-of-god/</guid>
      <description>Uruguay vs. Ghana Quarter final match - 2010 FIFA World Cup
I was sleepy, but somehow this match seemed too good to miss. I had to wash my face with cold water to stay awake. I must tell you, it was WORTH it. Much much more than WORTH it. An exciting match. Last few moments I had my heart in my mouth. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t supporting any of the teams, but still I feel heartbroken; Ghana should have won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Planned Visit Gone Wrong</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-planned-visit-gone-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 17:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-planned-visit-gone-wrong/</guid>
      <description>15th July 2010 Early morning – The shopkeeper A got a shocker when he opened the door. Some items inside the shop were displaced, the drawer opened, 200 Rupees missing. He informed my Dad - the shop owner. Since the door was locked and there was no sign of any damage to the door or the locks they decided that somebody has access to the keys or someone has got the duplicates done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Culinary Skills - I</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 20:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-i/</guid>
      <description>Keep the ingredients ready    I wanted to show off my culinary skill (if I have any 😛) the other day when I made a chicken dish, unfortunately, I forgot to post it. This was in draft mode for over 5 months now! I had completely forgotten about it until yesterday when I started preparing biriyani. Publishing it now, enjoy. 😃
If I&amp;rsquo;m not following the recipes, I will keep it very simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autosys and Unix Permission</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/autosys-and-unix-permission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 17:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/autosys-and-unix-permission/</guid>
      <description>Say Autosys job called jobName executes with xyz id. The profile used is profile; owner of profile is abc and neither group nor others have execute permission on this profile. jobName executes jobScript which is owned by xyz(both jobName and jobScript are owned by xyz). abc and xyz are two users. There is a group abc as well.
$id abc uid=1234(abc) gid=10(abc) $id xyz uid=1234(xyz) gid=10(users) $ll profile -r-xr+++-- 1 abc abc 1000 [.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate Torrent Download Using Transmission</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/automate-torrent-download-using-transmission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/automate-torrent-download-using-transmission/</guid>
      <description>A while ago I wrote about swget - A Simple wget Wrapper The methods described don&amp;rsquo;t work for torrents. Today I had to download a video which was not available through direct download, but I found a few torrents for the same. After fiddling around with the scheduler available in Transmission I found it to be absolutely useless; it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work!
After a little search on the net, I found a workaround for this too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My H1B Visa Stamping Saga - Part II</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 19:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>The day of stamping - My interview was schedule at 8:30AM and I was expected to be there by 8AM. The previous day night I set alarm for 6, 6:10, 6:15AM. My usual pattern even after which I don&amp;rsquo;t wake up! I slept through all three alarms and woke up when Mom called me to wish me at 7AM. The cab guy also called at the same time. Cleverly, I had ironed clothes and arranged documents in Bangalore itself; I got ready in just about 15 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My H1B Visa stamping Saga - Part I</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 17:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-i/</guid>
      <description>My H1B visa was approved in December 2009 and finally, I got to get it stamped on 18th May 2010. I had arranged all documents by last Thursday and booked air tickets to Chennai. I had never travelled by air before; it was going to be my first time. 😃
Monday morning I got a call from the cab driver who was lost trying to find me! After around 6-7 call and giving him directions, he finally made it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu 10.04 - Lucid Lynx</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/ubuntu-10-04-lucid-lynx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 18:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/ubuntu-10-04-lucid-lynx/</guid>
      <description>Very first impression(within a minute of installing):
 WTF, it hung!
 I had kept /home on a separate partition for the first time and wanted to check if it works fine for all users. I created an account and set the home folder as /home/irine and then hit save - switch user - log off - WTF!
Bug #574909
Ubuntu 10.04 (Lucid Lynx) is impressive; thanks to all those who made it possible :o)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Childhood memories</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/childhood-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 17:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/childhood-memories/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m feeling nostalgic today. Very much. I had lot of time at my hand and decided to clean up my cupboard, which I do from time to time. Until a few years back, I used to keep all things I used to have during my childhood days and one day I decided to get rid of all the junk. First time I did it, believe me, it was so painful. Each small item had so many memories associated with it, but I had to clean up stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Put My First GIMP Work To Use</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/how-i-put-my-first-gimp-work-to-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 12:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/how-i-put-my-first-gimp-work-to-use/</guid>
      <description>HotLinking. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what it means follow the link and spend a couple of minutes reading about it. For those who are not interested in doing so - hotlinking is somebody else riding your superbike on your petrol without your knowledge and without giving you any credit. Bad analogy? :o)
How do you make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t allow something which you don&amp;rsquo;t even know is happening? Very simple, using .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript CountUp Timer</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countup-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2010 13:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/javascript-countup-timer/</guid>
      <description>Update (2018): I have moved the code to GitHub - JavaScript Counters AS IS. 
I was in need of timer to mark an important decision; I did what most of us would do - search on the internet. I found quite a few of them, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t like any of them. Some of them were unnecessarily complicated; a couple of others weren&amp;rsquo;t easily understandable; most of them were using approximation (esp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quit Smoking</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/quit-smoking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 18:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/quit-smoking/</guid>
      <description>I started smoking, I guess, eight or nine years ago. For the initial four or five years it was more or less like two or three cigarettes a year, so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t a smoker then by any standard. :o) However, I really started smoking nearly three years ago.
I have been on and off at it. I quit smoking for a couple of months a couple of times in these three years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBMP Elections and Women Reservation</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/bbmp-elections-and-women-reservation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 19:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/bbmp-elections-and-women-reservation/</guid>
      <description>BBMP elections are scheduled for tomorrow. My ward is one of those wards reserved for women. That is nothing to be happy about! Reservation is a very noble plan with a pathetic implementation. I was trying to get as much information about the candidates as possible so that I can vote for the most eligible. There are seven women candidates contesting in the election from my ward. As far as I could see, all of them are wives or relatives of politically powerful men and I find most of them incapable!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Glass Painting</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-glass-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-glass-painting/</guid>
      <description>This is the glass painting I was talking about here.
   Lord Ganesha    The following two are made(on the window) by my brother.
   Glass painting on the window      Glass painting on the window    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swget - A Simple wget Wrapper</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/swget-a-simple-wget-wrapper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 19:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/swget-a-simple-wget-wrapper/</guid>
      <description>THE PROBLEM I have BSNL 500C+ broadband connection which gives me 2.5GB of data transfer per month. This limit is sufficient only for usual surfing. 500C+ plan also gives me night unlimited option i.e. the data transferred between 2AM to 8AM is not counted towards the 2.5GB quota per month. I can download around 4GB in this time frame. I use this time to download contents, but the real problem is starting the download at 2AM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Week That Was</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-week-that-was/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 19:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-week-that-was/</guid>
      <description>Last week was the crappiest of all, but it ended in a good note. It oscillated between okay to bad, bad to worse, and back to okay and then to good. First two days were uneventful and I had no clue of what lie ahead.
Wednesday was the beginning. Firstly, a brand new system welcomed me to office on Wednesday morning; they had formatted my machine without any kind of confirmation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Weekend In Mangalore</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 15:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</guid>
      <description>Update (2018): TMI galore!
Mangalore. Stirs up a lot of feeling. The first city, other than Bangalore, where I spent more than a year, the city where I lived independently, the city where I gained financial independence, the city where I started watching movies (for real!), the city which has given me a few best friends, the city where I fell in love&amp;hellip; I have so many fond memories of this city that I could go on and on and on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highest Runs In An ODI Match – Sachin Tendulkar</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/highest-runs-in-an-odi-match-sachin-tendulkar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 04:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/highest-runs-in-an-odi-match-sachin-tendulkar/</guid>
      <description>I have come across a lot of comments, communications, posts, and people (even my Dad and Bro) where they mention how they hated a Pakistani cricketer(Saeed Anwar) holding the record for highest ODI runs in a match. I don&amp;rsquo;t understand! A cricketer is a cricketer, a game is a game, a record is a record, what does it have to do with the citizenship?
What would you(esp. Indians) have called Sachin, if he was a Pakistani?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentine&#39;s Day Gift</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/valentines-day-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 18:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/valentines-day-gift/</guid>
      <description>This valentine&amp;rsquo;s day she was very happy. She has been with me for quite long time now; I had never seen her so happy and excited in before. As I type this post she is on call and I can clearly hear her sharing it with her sister and this is her third call! :o)
Though she&amp;rsquo;d never tell me, I always knew that she wanted it. She is very interested in stitching, embroidery, and other creative stuff which mainly deals with fabric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Nuts</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/3-nuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 19:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/3-nuts/</guid>
      <description>The title is inspired by the movie 3 Idiots which the world around me is going gaga over. The picture was clicked over the weekend with a point &amp;amp; shoot camera when I was going mad with boredom. Reason for posting this? I don&amp;rsquo;t know! I started experimenting with GIMP and I have provided both versions of the picture.
   3 nuts - Unedited      3 nuts - Edited    This is not my first GIMP work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OS Switch: Fedora to Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/os-switch-fedora-to-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 16:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/os-switch-fedora-to-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>A post about switching the Operating System(OS)? Yeah, why not? After all It&amp;rsquo;s the OS that made one man the richest in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s the OS that has made so many people across the globe dedicate their own resources and time to better it. It&amp;rsquo;s the OS that makes people argue - be it MS vs Linux or different distributions of Linux itself!
I&amp;rsquo;m not a Linux freak or a guru but an average user helping the open source in a way that most of the people do - by using it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Physique &amp; Polio-stricken Chicken&#39;s Leg</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/good-physique-polio-stricken-chickens-leg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 07:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/good-physique-polio-stricken-chickens-leg/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether to be happy or doubtful when a stranger walks up to me in the gym and
  Stranger
 :  Hey   Me :  Hi   Stranger :  You are regular here?   Me :  (have you ever seen me here earlier?) No. Second day in this gym.   Stranger :  Oh okay.   Me :  Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another &#34;Hello, world!&#34;?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/yet-another-hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 19:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/yet-another-hello-world/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m bored of Hello, world!; I did that over
 9000 days 1300 weeks 200,000 hours 13,000,000 minutes 750,000,000 seconds  ago. Yeah, about 25 years ago, I did my personal Hello, world!
 Hello, world!
 Yet another &amp;ldquo;Hello, world!&amp;rdquo;? Yes, this time not from me but from this very blog you are reading! :o)
On a serious note, I&amp;rsquo;m very happy to start this blog, it was one of the items pending on my Bucket List for a long time now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>