<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>run on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/run/</link>
    <description>Recent content in run on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 17:44:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/run/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Have I Been Up To This Summer?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 17:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>It has been a long time since I blogged regularly. We have a couple of weeks of summer left in 2012 and I don’t want to waste that spending more time on blogging. Lately, I have been feeling like blogging is a winter activity (not saying that I blog regularly in winter). There are a number of topics blog about but no time. I keep adding topics to the todo list and keep deleting when I revisit because it’s either too late or it is making the list too big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>34th Roots &amp; Wings Annual Run/Walk 2011</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/34th-roots-wings-annual-runwalk-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 05:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/34th-roots-wings-annual-runwalk-2011/</guid>
      <description>Facebook status on July 24 at 12:40am
 1750 to beat.
 Facebook status on July 24 at 9:57am
 1753 seconds to finish; just 3 seconds dammit.
 Says it all, doesn&#39;t it?
  Roots &amp;amp; Wings T-Shirt
   It was the 34th Roots &amp;amp; Wings Annual Run/Walk 2011 (in Milwaukee marks the beginning of the Northwestern Mutual&#39;s Annual Meeting of the Association of Network Representatives) and there I was a good 5 minutes late at the start line!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm The Bastille 2011 - Milwaukee</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/storm-the-bastille-2011-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 05:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/storm-the-bastille-2011-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>The Bastille, the medieval fortress and prison in Paris, was stormed by the demonstrators to acquire the ammunition on 14 July 1789. This day marks the start of the French Revolution and is celebrated as a national holiday in France. The same is celebrated in across the world. One such place is Milwaukee. Yes, the place I live now!
 Bastille Days is North America&#39;s largest outdoor French themed festival held in downtown Milwaukee in Cathedral Square Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lost Track</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-lost-track-on-the-streets-of-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 05:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-lost-track-on-the-streets-of-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m one of those lazy ones when it comes to gym or jogging. I don&#39;t even remember when I jogged last. Gym has been on and off with a total I can count with my fingers of one hand. After all it&#39;s for those who want to be fit; not for those who are already fit. 😉
Anyhow, I started practicing for a 5K run scheduled for June 24th Sunday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>