<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cooking on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/cooking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cooking on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 06:41:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/cooking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Indians Are The World Champions</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 06:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</guid>
      <description>You know by now. Indians are the world champions! Yeah, say that again, WE ARE THE CHAMPIONS!
Remember &amp;ldquo;More than a billion hearts and one shared dream&amp;rdquo;? That&#39;s what I wrote when the world cup started. That dream has come true! Now more than 50% of Indian population can proudly say they saw their captain lift the world cup at least once in their life. Glory!
Homepage mania: I dedicated the homepage to Green Bay Packers and they won the super bowl; they are the Champions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing Chocolate Brownie</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/preparing-chocolate-brownie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 23:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/preparing-chocolate-brownie/</guid>
      <description>This is Sunday afternoon, I&#39;m bored and I&#39;m planning to prepare Chocolate Brownies. I have never prepared it before and looking at the instructions on the pack, I must say it is not big deal at all. All you need is, well, Chocolate Brownie mix, some eggs and vegetable oil. I&#39;m off.
PS: Okay, I don&#39;t have anything to blog about. Big deal. 😝
  Brownies in the tray</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eat Oatmeal Idiots</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</guid>
      <description>I know, the subject is a bit harsh, but it&#39;s well suited for all comments I get from my room-mates about eating oats. Oats is one of the food that I just love. I first started having oatmeal three years ago when I came across many articles on the net. I felt like, it was made for me! Why? It&#39;s simple, easy to prepare, healthy.
Believe it or not with very little or no exercise I was able to cut down all fat and lose weight just by controlling eating habits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Culinary Skills - III</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 05:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-iii/</guid>
      <description>Another one from the old drafts. Only pictures this time. :-)
  Step 1
    Step 2
    Step 3
    Step 4
    Step 5
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Culinary Skills - II</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2010 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-ii/</guid>
      <description>This was in draft mode for over 5 months now! There is something with me and updating this blog. There are a couple of more drafts. I plan to post all of them in next two weeks.
If I&#39;m not following the recipes which I read somewhere, I will keep it very simple. First I check what are the items I can use, then etch a plan, pick the items, and cook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Culinary Skills - I</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 20:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-i/</guid>
      <description>Keep the ingredients ready
   I wanted to show off my culinary skill (if I have any 😛) the other day when I made a chicken dish, unfortunately, I forgot to post it. This was in draft mode for over 5 months now! I had completely forgotten about it until yesterday when I started preparing biriyani. Publishing it now, enjoy. 😃
If I&#39;m not following the recipes, I will keep it very simple.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>