<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Winter on Praveen Lobo</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/winter/</link><description>Recent content in Winter on Praveen Lobo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 19:10:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/winter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weather comparison</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/weather-comparison-bangalore-vs-milwaukee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 19:10:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/weather-comparison-bangalore-vs-milwaukee/</guid><description>&lt;p>You know by now, &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/doesnt-this-weather-remind-you-of-india/">I&amp;rsquo;m a bit concerned about this weather&lt;/a>. While checking the weather forecast, I came up with this idea of comparing the weather between Bangalore and Milwaukee. Just for giggles.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>The below graphs are drawn with the data available freely on the net(weather.com, wikipedia and wunderground.com). I believe they should be fairly accurate.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/34-summer/Bangalore%20vs%20Milwaukee%20-%20Weather%28F%29.png"
 alt="Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°F)">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°F)&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/34-summer/Bangalore%20vs%20Milwaukee%20-%20Weather%28C%29.png"
 alt="Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°C)">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°C)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Doesn't this weather remind you of India?</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/doesnt-this-weather-remind-you-of-india/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 23:44:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/doesnt-this-weather-remind-you-of-india/</guid><description>&lt;p>The weather has been truly devastating this summer (Milwaukee 2011). National Weather Service issued heat advisory; many sources reminding the deadly heat from 1995 and 1988 which took a lot of lives! The weather forecasts, news-sites, and other sources of information on the internet are terrifying.&lt;/p>
&lt;h5 id="rewind-to-2010">Rewind to 2010&lt;/h5>
&lt;p>I landed exactly one year ago in Milwaukee. The weather was not bad. It compared to the weather I was used to in Bangalore. I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice much difference at all. Move forward to Fall, I was being constantly warned about the winter ahead! I kept hearing this for a long time as the winter arrived very late.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Ski Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 02:43:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/lobo.jpg"
 alt="Lobo(Ski Brule)">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Lobo(Ski Brule)&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/Buckhorn%20Chalet.jpg"
 alt="Buckhorn Chalet">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>Around twenty of us drove up to Ski Brule, Iron River Michigan, on Thursday and stayed at &lt;strong>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/strong> right in front of the slopes. The slopes looked so beautiful and scary at the same time. I was excited to ski for the first time the very next day.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/on%20the%20bunny.jpg"
 alt="With Staff on bunny hills">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>With Staff on bunny hills&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>When we reached there, there was a free lessons for first timers (should register beforehand). The faculty was nice enough to allow me to join even-though I had not registered. They had first-timers-ski-free offer as well which I missed! Anyway, the faculty was helping the inexperienced on the bunny hills in using the ropes, sliding, stopping, turning. They answered my questions, helped me get up, skied down the slope along with me, helped me tremendously in getting used to the rope (this was so difficult at first, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go more than two feet) and were very cheerful. Now when I think of it, I liked the skiing experience because of their good faculty as well. Thumbs up for them. &amp;#x1f44d;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>First Winter in Milwaukee</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 06:30:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</guid><description>&lt;p>Just when I started to laugh at people who were scaring me about the winter, mother nature made sure I shut up. It was a total pain to walk 6 blocks back home from office today! The main problem is the wind. If it isn&amp;rsquo;t for the wind chill factor, the winter is not much of a problem.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s getting freaking cold here in Milwaukee; it&amp;rsquo;s expected to hit -8°F(-22°C) tomorrow and with the wind and other factors, it&amp;rsquo;s expected to feel like -27°F(-32°C). To say the least, that sucks!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>