<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>0 on Praveen Lobo</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/categories/0/</link><description>Recent content in 0 on Praveen Lobo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/categories/0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>To Refinance Or Not To Refinance</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/mortgage-loan-and-refinancing-comparison/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/mortgage-loan-and-refinancing-comparison/</guid><description>&lt;p>Like nearly every home owner right about now in America, we were thinking about refinancing and called our mortgage bank contact. He compared our current loan and what we could refinance it for and said that we would save about $12,000. I wanted to do a little bit of research before going ahead as I had not done any!&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="before-i-explain">Before I Explain&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Please note that this is not an article that tells you whether you should or shouldn&amp;rsquo;t refinance. You should do your own research and decide based on your own circumstances and probably consult professionals who do this for a living. You should also read from websites run by people who do this type of work day in and day out. However, you may use the mortgage loan refinance calculator I built to do a detailed comparison. I think the calculator I built is more detailed than anything else I could find. If you find a more detailed calculator, please leave a comment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>US Presidential Elections</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/us-presidential-election-2016-trump-card/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 03:47:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/us-presidential-election-2016-trump-card/</guid><description>&lt;p>The 2016 US presidential election campaigns are underway, and they are very entertaining! I do not know to the full extent how this entire presidential election works. I doubt if many of the US citizens even understand how this works! So, I spent a couple of hours on this topic and decided to write about it. If you find any inaccuracies, I will be glad to fix it!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>US presidential elections are important not just for the Americans but also for the rest of the world. We live in a world where a political change in one part of the world can have a big impact on some other parts of the world. When it comes to US, a dominant force in the world, any political change impacts nearly every part of the globe, and it is important that we, the rest of the world, know how the elections work!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>HOLY CRAP!!!</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holy-crap-missing-in-action/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 20:58:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holy-crap-missing-in-action/</guid><description>&lt;p>HOLY MOTHER OF SWEET BABY CORN! It has seriously been a long while! 3 years? 4 years? Surprised the blog still exists! LOL! Actually not that much surprised. I pay every year to renew hosting so I know it exists! &amp;#x1f61b;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The TODO list thing I do. Seriously, it has gotten out of hand! I have unfinished drafts from 2011, 2012, 2013 which are still not posted! I feel embarrassed; at the same time I feel overwhelmed thinking how fast the time flies!
Four fucking years! Seriously?!?!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What Have I Been Up To This Summer?</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 17:44:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</guid><description>&lt;p>It has been a long time since I blogged regularly. We have a couple of weeks of summer left in 2012 and I don’t want to waste that spending more time on blogging. Lately, I have been feeling like blogging is a winter activity (not saying that I blog regularly in winter). There are a number of topics blog about but no time. I keep adding topics to the todo list and keep deleting when I revisit because it’s either too late or it is making the list too big. This has been my story for past year or so. I can’t sit down and just do it. Maybe I should fix a schedule and stick to it. I don’t know.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Ride Lobo Ride - UPAF Ride For The Arts 2012</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/ride-lobo-ride-upaf-ride-for-the-arts-2012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 16:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/ride-lobo-ride-upaf-ride-for-the-arts-2012/</guid><description>&lt;p>Over quarter of a million participants have taken part in annual United Performing Arts Fund (UPAF) Ride for the Arts since 1981. According to UPAF, which provides financial support to 36 beneficiary groups, the ride helps keep the performing arts scene dynamic and a vital part of the community&amp;rsquo;s culture and that they are among the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest united arts funds in terms of dollars raised and number of donors.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Second Bicycle</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-second-bicycle-a-2012-trek-ds-8-3-bicycle-from-wheel-and-sprocket-bike-expo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 03:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-second-bicycle-a-2012-trek-ds-8-3-bicycle-from-wheel-and-sprocket-bike-expo/</guid><description>&lt;p>I used to &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-bicycle-hercules-mtb-bangalore-year-2000/">love bicycles&lt;/a> until I started working and moved on to ride motorbikes. Motorbikes were convenient, affordable, and fast. I had bought myself a TVS Suzuki Fiero DS (India&amp;rsquo;s first 150cc bike I think) and I was using it for everyday commute. I had sold my first bicycle and didn&amp;rsquo;t have one to ride. As it happens as one grows up, I had given up on bicycles.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After moving to US, I live very close walk to work and don&amp;rsquo;t need any vehicles for travel. Then there is always new rental cars at cheap rates if need be. Milwaukee downtown is not that big and I can easily walk to almost all places. However, commuting around downtown (like going to lake side, tennis courts, or coffee shop) really made me think about the bicycles again.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My First Bicycle - An Hercules MTB</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-bicycle-hercules-mtb-bangalore-year-2000/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 01:50:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-bicycle-hercules-mtb-bangalore-year-2000/</guid><description>&lt;p>As a kid I was jealous of my brother, my cousin, and all my friends (who knew how to ride a bicycle). I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to ride a bike until I was thirteen or fourteen I think. My mom was too scared to allow me to ride a bicycle. I&amp;rsquo;d lie to mom and go trying to ride a bike instead of playing. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember anyone helping me how to ride. I somehow learnt by borrowing/renting bicycles on my own. We could rent bicycles from &lt;em>cycle shops&lt;/em> for one or two rupees for an hour and as soon as I collected enough money, I&amp;rsquo;d run the cycle shops, rent a bike. It was indeed liberating to just bike away and explore the part of the villages that I had never seen before.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>I'm An Indian Green Bay Packer Owner!</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/im-an-indian-green-bay-packer-owner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 03:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/im-an-indian-green-bay-packer-owner/</guid><description>&lt;p>Well, the magic spell is over! Packers won 19 consecutive games before I ever saw them lose. It was rather disappointing to see them lose against Chiefs; it was heartbreaking to see them lose in the very first game of the playoffs. That doesn’t deter me from calling myself a Packer fan.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Oh, wait a minute, I’m not just a fan; I’m a mutual owner of Green Bay Packers! I own a part of NFL’s most mesmerizing team - the Green Bay Packers. I was just wondering if there are other Indians who own Green Bay Packers’ stock? Surely, there must be more!?!?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Daylight Saving Time (DST)</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/daylight-saving-time-dst-should-be-a-part-of-our-history/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 02:03:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/daylight-saving-time-dst-should-be-a-part-of-our-history/</guid><description>&lt;p>I was having a conversation with a friend of mine who is convinced that the Daylight Saving Time (DST) change is good and makes perfect sense. I, for one, think that the DST is not useful anymore and it could have been avoided altogether. Just imagine if we didn’t have clocks and a way to time. We would have adjusted our lifestyles automatically to adapt to the nature. Instead of adjusting the clock, we should have adjusted the schedules.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Will Google Voice be free in 2012 and beyond?</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/will-google-voice-be-free-in-2012-and-beyond/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/will-google-voice-be-free-in-2012-and-beyond/</guid><description>&lt;p>From the &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/does-google-voice-use-minutes-or-data/">recent notes&lt;/a> I made on the Google Voice and how it uses the carrier minutes and data to operate, it should be free in 2012 and beyond.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Why? Currently, Google Voice is not a VOIP service and it uses the carrier minutes and data to operate which means to make or receive calls the subscriber has to pay the carrier. See the image in &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/does-google-voice-use-minutes-or-data/">that&lt;/a> post. If Google Voice doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer VOIP service and starts charging for the voice calls, the subscriber will be &lt;em>double charged&lt;/em>. For every call made or received, the subscriber has to pay to use Google Voice and then, since Google Voice uses the carrier minutes, has to pay the carrier for using the minutes. If this is exactly how it works, it will be very difficult to justify Google Voice. I&amp;rsquo;d definitely drop Google Voice and, I think, many other will do too.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Does Google Voice Use Minutes or Data?</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/does-google-voice-use-minutes-or-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 05:55:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/does-google-voice-use-minutes-or-data/</guid><description>&lt;p>Does Google Voice Use Minutes or Data? Does Google Voice cost money? How does Google Voice calling or texting work? The answer is Yes, Yes, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Update: See &lt;a href="https://support.google.com/voice/answer/115063?hl=en">this&lt;/a> for more info&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Google Voice is an awesome idea and piece of software (if you are willing to give away more self information to Google than you already have). It is not a VOIP service like Google Talk; it is a call management service. It will always cost you money in one way or the other (cellular minutes or data) and you will not be able to make free calls. If you consider cellular data to be free or use wifi, there are workarounds to make it free like using Talkatone or GrooVe IP or other third party apps. These applications use Google Talk free calling feature (VOIP) along with Google Voice, which integrates with Google Talk, to make free calls using only data. Keep in mind that by using more services, you are distributing your own information all over the Internet companies.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What Was My Skydiving All About?</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 05:40:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-was-my-skydiving-all-about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ever since I posted my skydiving post/video and dedicated it to the people fighting against corruption, some of my friends have been teasing me about it. I did what I wanted to and have no regrets. I have been able to shut them up with just asking if they have the balls to do it before talking smack!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I can take a good tease but the attitude of getting things done quickly and avoiding lines even if it means paying bribe irks me to the core. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind having a healthy discussion, but with some so determined to pay bribe to get things done quickly and wholeheartedly oppose anyone who fights corruption, any discussion is a waste of time and energy. Many of my American friends are optimistic and talk positively (esp. knowing the Gandhi episode), but many of my own countrymen are very very skeptical and pessimistic. If well educated people don&amp;rsquo;t support a cause and act overly smart, what do you think will change? Everything has to start some way and someday, why not make this a starting point for a good future?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>An Anonymous Halloween</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/an-anonymous-halloween-2011/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2011 16:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/an-anonymous-halloween-2011/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/47-halloween/Tombstone%20and%20eyeballs.jpg"
 alt="Tombstone and eyeballs cupcakes">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Tombstone and eyeballs cupcakes&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>It was that time of the year again when the pumpkins are carved, people get costumed, and walk around downtown, of course, showing off. Guess what I did different this time - I carved a pumpkin! The family I was with loves cars so I thought of carving a Mustang (they own one). I made a sketch of it from a picture I had taken of their car, but decided not to do it as it&amp;rsquo;d be difficult and was probably going to take more time. I left the sketch at home and when I reached there, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to carve other than a smiley face. So, I just decided to go for the Mustang carving with the sketch out of my mind. It didn&amp;rsquo;t turn out to be a Mustang not even close, but it looks like a car at least. See them below. Oh, that&amp;rsquo;s them driving the car. &amp;#x1f604;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Deepavali in Milwaukee</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/deepavali-in-milwaukee-2011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/deepavali-in-milwaukee-2011/</guid><description>&lt;p>My second Deepavali in Milwaukee. Celebrated by visiting temple, doing a small pooja at home and then at a friend’s place. Prepared gulab jamun, had lot of wonderful food at potluck in friend’s place. Concluded it with firecrackers.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My roommates kept American dollars next to Indian rupees on the alter. I wonder what they were praying for. &amp;#x1f61d;&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/46-deepavali/deepavali.jpg"
 alt="Deepavali 2011, Milwaukee">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Deepavali 2011, Milwaukee&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>I tried roller blading</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-tried-roller-blading/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 05:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-tried-roller-blading/</guid><description>&lt;p>On the Sweetest Day of 2011, I just happened to visit the Incredi-Roll Skate &amp;amp; Laser Tag Family Fun Center (on Oklahoma) for some rollerblade fun. I always wanted to &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/bucket-list/">learn rollerblading&lt;/a>. A friend of mine forced me to get into it for sometime before giving up on me. But this sweetest day, I gave it a try. It&amp;rsquo;s indoors so there&amp;rsquo;s no danger of getting run over by a truck. How many people might be there for the embarrassment part? I thought may be 10-15, but boy, I was wrong! This place was full of people. People on rollerskates, rollerblades. Zipping through the center.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Perfect Season - Green Bay Packers</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-perfect-season-green-bay-packers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 18:11:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-perfect-season-green-bay-packers/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Elle Meissner - The Lions haven’t won a championship since her grandfather was 5 and haven’t won a playoff game since her father was 10, in her lifetime, the Detroit Lions haven’t lost a game.
&lt;a href="http://www.mlive.com/sports/bay-city/index.ssf/2011/10/detroit_lions_finally_find_the.html">more&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>This news reminded me that I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen a single game that Green Bay Packers lost! The first time I heard of American Football was at the end of 2006 in a session helping people understand the basics of the game. It was conducted by one of my senior colleague in Mangalore office. I never really got interested until I moved to Milwaukee in 2010. I kept on hearing about football for months before I really followed anything.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>It Needs A Genius To Understand The Simplicity</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/it-needs-a-genius-to-understand-the-simplicity-r-i-p-dennis-ritchie/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 02:41:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/it-needs-a-genius-to-understand-the-simplicity-r-i-p-dennis-ritchie/</guid><description>&lt;p>U changed the world; it is because of the people like you we C the world the way it is today. You didn&amp;rsquo;t make billions, but billionaires. You have such an impact not only on those who lived in your lifetime, but also on those who are yet to C the light of the day. Your influence is ubiquitous. The mankind will forever be grateful to you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>R.I.P. Dennis Ritchie.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My First Game At The Lambeau Field</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-game-at-the-lambeau-field-packers-vs-saints/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 01:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-first-game-at-the-lambeau-field-packers-vs-saints/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-visit-to-the-frozen-tundra-lambeau-field/">As I mentioned earlier&lt;/a>, I was able to get the tickets for the opening game of the season on September 8th, 2011. The world champions take on the New Orleans Saints. We also managed to make some time to visit the hall of fame. One thing I learned during this visit was the super bowl ring is not given just to the players but also to coaches, trainers, executives, personnel, and general staff! The winning team can present the rings to whomever they choose.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Visit To The Frozen Tundra</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-visit-to-the-frozen-tundra-lambeau-field/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 01:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-visit-to-the-frozen-tundra-lambeau-field/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/44-lambeau-visit/Lambeau%20Field.jpg"
 alt="Lambeau Field">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Lambeau Field&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>I have driven around the stadium once while returning from the Door County last fall. This time while returning from a &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-trip-to-pictured-rocks-michigan">trip to Pictured Rocks&lt;/a>, I visited the Lambeau Field a.k.a The Frozen Tundra and took a tour of the stadium. It was just so unbelievable to be there and to learn some history about the Packers. I even got a customized replica jersey and a Packer&amp;rsquo;s Rubik cube among other things.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Trip To Pictured Rocks, Michigan</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-trip-to-pictured-rocks-michigan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 04:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-trip-to-pictured-rocks-michigan/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/43-pictured-rocks/En%20route.jpg">
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>Pictured Rocks is a U.S. National Lakeshore on the shore of Lake Superior in the Upper Peninsula of Michigan. It is a beautiful place up north, just google and you won’t disagree. Kayaking in the sea? Wouldn’t it be amazing? We set to find out.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/43-pictured-rocks/Car.jpg"
 alt="Rental Car">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Rental Car&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>&lt;strong>Plan&lt;/strong>: On the September long weekend (Labor day holiday) start from Milwaukee on Saturday, explore Mackinac Island, Pictured Rocks sea kayaking on Sunday, and sightseeing and returning on Monday.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Do It Now, or You Might Never Get A Chance Again</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/do-it-now-or-you-might-never-get-a-chance-again/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 05:58:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/do-it-now-or-you-might-never-get-a-chance-again/</guid><description>&lt;p>Finally on August 20th, 2011, I skydived for the first time, not only unheeding my friends&amp;rsquo; suggestions to go for tandem first and then solo/Accelerated Free Fall (AFF) but also my own fear of jumping into the unknown. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how it will be to fall from 14,000 feet, descending at 120MPH (193KMPH). I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if the instructors will be able to guide me ntil the pull; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if the parachute will open fine or not; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if I would land on Interstate-94 and get dragged down the road.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Story Of My Childhood</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-story-of-my-childhood/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 04:54:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-story-of-my-childhood/</guid><description>&lt;p>Last weekend, I had one of my friend come over from Chicago. I hadn&amp;rsquo;t met him in nearly 6-7 years until a couple of days ago when I met him Chicago. We went skydiving, and visited Lake Geneva and had good time together. Meeting him brought back many memories from my childhood and school days and inspired me to write. I think, it&amp;rsquo;s time to share and put them down here before they are completely erased from my already weak memories. So, here it goes, arranged in order with my failing recollection of my childhood&amp;hellip;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A 21 Year Old Friendship</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2011 07:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-21-year-old-friendship/</guid><description>&lt;p>Krishnamurthy. He is my oldest friend. We were in same class in Bangalore for six years starting 1990 before I had to leave. We were not in touch and had not met more than a handful of times in the last fifteen years. Then when I met him, he was still the same! He had moved to a new place and before I knew it, he was gone from there. I tried to find him but in vain.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>I Paid A Bribe Once</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-paid-a-bribe-once/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 05:44:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/i-paid-a-bribe-once/</guid><description>&lt;p>When I was growing up, I used to read the articles in the newspaper about people returning the money/jewelry that somebody else had lost, the auto driver returning thousands of rupees the passengers had left behind. I used to wonder what made them do what they did especially when the person who did it was indeed very poor. Why didn&amp;rsquo;t s/he keep it her/himself, used it to feed his family, made a life out of it. One moment I would think, returning it made no sense at all and the next moment I would just imagine the plight of the people who lost it. What if someone lost all their hard earned money, a life time of savings, what if if was from a poor father carrying it to arrange for his daughter&amp;rsquo;s wedding? It made perfect sense to return it. The happiness that it&amp;rsquo;d bring when one loses something precious and find it later; the good feel that it&amp;rsquo;d instill in one&amp;rsquo;s heart; the give-back/do-the-same-thing attitude that it&amp;rsquo;d bring seemed much more valuable than the actual item&amp;rsquo;s worth.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>One Hell Of A Tiring Weekend</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/one-hell-of-a-tiring-weekend-skydive-plan-gone-wrong-and-lake-geneva-again/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 03:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/one-hell-of-a-tiring-weekend-skydive-plan-gone-wrong-and-lake-geneva-again/</guid><description>&lt;p>If everything went according to the plan, I&amp;rsquo;d have had my first ever free-fall by now. But the mother nature had some other plans. Six friends and I had planned for a skydiving weekend on my room-mate&amp;rsquo;s birthday last Saturday. Two of them had come down from Chicago. The venue was none other than the closest &lt;a href="http://www.skydivemidwest.com/">Skydive Midwest&lt;/a>. None of us had previous experience and were looking forward to having a great time. We reached the place a couple of minutes after our scheduled time and registered at the manifest. Basically, we just put our lives on the line and signed contracts saying Skydive Midwest will not be liable for any accidents. Six of us were to do tandem jumps and I solo (Accelerated Free Fall - AFF). Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me why I decided to jump solo; I don&amp;rsquo;t know!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Camping At Big Foot Beach State Park</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-big-foot-beach-state-park-lake-geneva/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 01:36:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-big-foot-beach-state-park-lake-geneva/</guid><description>&lt;p>Another summer, another camping. This time at &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps?client=ubuntu&amp;amp;channel=cs&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;q=Big&amp;#43;Foot&amp;#43;State&amp;#43;Park,&amp;#43;Lake&amp;#43;Geneva&amp;amp;fb=1&amp;amp;gl=us&amp;amp;hq=Big&amp;#43;Foot&amp;#43;State&amp;#43;Park,&amp;amp;hnear=0x880584e9f85c4509:0x9eb9a6efc12afe43,Lake&amp;#43;Geneva,&amp;#43;WI&amp;amp;cid=0,0,7166353873496965653&amp;amp;ll=42.574321,-88.438568&amp;amp;spn=0.126411,0.343323&amp;amp;z=11&amp;amp;source=embed">Big Foot Beach State Park, Lake Geneva&lt;/a>. It is located very close to the lake and is right in the city. Four of us camped from Friday evening to Sunday morning with two friends visting Saturday night.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Some pictures from camping at Big Foot beach State Park.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/tent.jpg"
 alt="Tent">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Tent&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/fire.jpg"
 alt="Campfire">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Campfire&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/moonlit%20sky.jpg"
 alt="Sky">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Sky&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/some%20trail.jpg"
 alt="Some Trail">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Some Trail&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/swing.jpg"
 alt="Swing">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Swing&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/37-lake-geneva-camping/soda.jpg"
 alt="Soda Vending Machine!">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Soda Vending Machine!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Three Rules to Excel at Work</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/three-rules-to-excel-at-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 04:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/three-rules-to-excel-at-work/</guid><description>&lt;p>My day at work had just began, when I overheard a colleague of mine talking about rule number two. He is very senior to me and is dangerously intelligent! I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop myself from asking him what the rule number two was.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Hey, what is rule number two?&amp;rdquo;, I asked.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Well, do you know rule number one?&amp;rdquo;, he questioned.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I replied, &amp;ldquo;Nope&amp;rdquo;, thinking why didn&amp;rsquo;t I ask about rule number one first!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>34th Roots &amp; Wings Annual Run/Walk 2011</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/34th-roots-wings-annual-runwalk-2011/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 05:15:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/34th-roots-wings-annual-runwalk-2011/</guid><description>&lt;p>Facebook status on July 24 at 12:40am&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>1750 to beat.&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Facebook status on July 24 at 9:57am&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>1753 seconds to finish; just 3 seconds dammit.&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Says it all, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/35-roots-wings/tshirt.jpg"
 alt="Roots &amp;amp; Wings T-Shirt">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Roots &amp;amp; Wings T-Shirt&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>It was the 34th Roots &amp;amp; Wings Annual Run/Walk 2011 (in Milwaukee marks the beginning of the Northwestern Mutual&amp;rsquo;s Annual Meeting of the Association of Network Representatives) and there I was a good 5 minutes late at the start line!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Weather comparison</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/weather-comparison-bangalore-vs-milwaukee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 19:10:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/weather-comparison-bangalore-vs-milwaukee/</guid><description>&lt;p>You know by now, &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/doesnt-this-weather-remind-you-of-india/">I&amp;rsquo;m a bit concerned about this weather&lt;/a>. While checking the weather forecast, I came up with this idea of comparing the weather between Bangalore and Milwaukee. Just for giggles.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>The below graphs are drawn with the data available freely on the net(weather.com, wikipedia and wunderground.com). I believe they should be fairly accurate.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/34-summer/Bangalore%20vs%20Milwaukee%20-%20Weather%28F%29.png"
 alt="Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°F)">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°F)&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/34-summer/Bangalore%20vs%20Milwaukee%20-%20Weather%28C%29.png"
 alt="Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°C)">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Bangalore vs Milwaukee - Weather(°C)&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Doesn't this weather remind you of India?</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/doesnt-this-weather-remind-you-of-india/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 23:44:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/doesnt-this-weather-remind-you-of-india/</guid><description>&lt;p>The weather has been truly devastating this summer (Milwaukee 2011). National Weather Service issued heat advisory; many sources reminding the deadly heat from 1995 and 1988 which took a lot of lives! The weather forecasts, news-sites, and other sources of information on the internet are terrifying.&lt;/p>
&lt;h5 id="rewind-to-2010">Rewind to 2010&lt;/h5>
&lt;p>I landed exactly one year ago in Milwaukee. The weather was not bad. It compared to the weather I was used to in Bangalore. I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice much difference at all. Move forward to Fall, I was being constantly warned about the winter ahead! I kept hearing this for a long time as the winter arrived very late.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Storm The Bastille 2011 - Milwaukee</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/storm-the-bastille-2011-milwaukee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 05:28:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/storm-the-bastille-2011-milwaukee/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Bastille, the medieval fortress and prison in Paris, was stormed by the demonstrators to acquire the ammunition on 14 July 1789. This day marks the start of the French Revolution and is celebrated as a national holiday in France. The same is celebrated in across the world. One such place is Milwaukee. Yes, the place I live now!&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Bastille Days is North America&amp;rsquo;s largest outdoor French themed festival held in downtown Milwaukee in Cathedral Square Park. &lt;a href="http://easttown.com/events/bastille-days">more&amp;hellip;&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Lost Track</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-lost-track-on-the-streets-of-milwaukee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 05:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-lost-track-on-the-streets-of-milwaukee/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m one of those lazy ones when it comes to gym or jogging. I don&amp;rsquo;t even remember when I jogged last. Gym has been on and off with a total I can count with my fingers of one hand. After all it&amp;rsquo;s for those who want to be fit; not for those who are already fit. &amp;#x1f609;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anyhow, I started practicing for a 5K run scheduled for June 24th Sunday morning. I jogged 3 times in last 10 days. First two were short, may be 2 miles each. The last one went crazy and that is what this post all about!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Abused</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/abused/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 05:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/abused/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/26-50/31-sketch/Abused.jpg"
 alt="Abused">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Abused&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>&lt;em>From archives. Not my original imagination.&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>H1B Interview Questions</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/h1b-interview-questions-chennai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 04:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/h1b-interview-questions-chennai/</guid><description>&lt;p>I had an H1B interview more than an year ago and written two blog posts about my travel to and from Bangalore and stay in Chennai (&lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-i/">here&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-ii/">here&lt;/a>). Surprisingly, even today &amp;ldquo;h1b&amp;rdquo; is one of the keywords getting highest number of visitors to my site (per Google Analytics). Most of them looking for interview questions. Recently I found a list I had prepared of probable questions the interviewer may ask. So, here goes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Small Gift Box For Me, Pain In The Neck For Most</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-small-gift-box-for-me-pain-in-the-neck-for-most/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-small-gift-box-for-me-pain-in-the-neck-for-most/</guid><description>&lt;p>Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I really don&amp;rsquo;t mean most by &amp;ldquo;most&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s just the most I encountered here. The other day I had to send some gifts through one of my friend who was travelling in next couple of hours. The idiot that I am, I had forgotten to buy the gift boxes! So, I decided to make them myself. I had just about everything it takes - some cardboard boxes, gift wrap, glue, a pair of scissors, and mighty interest.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 02:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-2/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="niagara-new-york-united-states">Niagara, New York, United States&lt;/h4>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/29-niagara/Terrapin%20Point%202.jpg"
 alt="Terrapin Point, Goat Island">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Terrapin Point, Goat Island&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>The next day as planned we drove to Niagara falls. There were a lot of people; I could see a lot of Indians as well. You probably won&amp;rsquo;t believe me but I met my a friend from my college (India) with his friends on Goat Island, I had no clue he was also visiting. Then I met another friend of mine from Bangalore on the Observation Tower! My friends were right when they said be prepared to see the place full of &lt;em>desis&lt;/em>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Niagara Falls and Cedar Point Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 04:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/niagara-falls-and-cedar-point-trip-day-1/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="cedar-point-sandusky-ohio-united-states">Cedar Point, Sandusky, Ohio, United States.&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>During the long weekend of September 2010, I visited Cedar Point and Niagara falls along with three other friends. It was an awesome trip. We took a flight from Milwaukee to Cleveland Ohio and rented a car from airport for the entire trip. The plan was to go to Cedar Point one day, visit Niagara next day, and head back the day after.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>First we drove to Cedar Point (Sandusky Ohio) from Marriott (Cleveland Airport Marriott). It was already noon by the time we reached there. It looked a bit scary from outside. All those roller coasters, best in America rankings, and &lt;em>never-before-sat-in-a-roller-coaster&lt;/em> feeling. Once we were inside there were huge lines near all coasters and rides. It was obvious that we would not be able to cover all of it especially because my friend and I wanted to sit at the very front in all rides that we take that day. So, we decided to hit the best of Cedar Point.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dark Blue/Light Blue Maps of India</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/dark-blue-light-blue-maps-of-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 05:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/dark-blue-light-blue-maps-of-india/</guid><description>&lt;p>These are the India maps I created* when designing &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/">my homepage for the grand 2011 Cricket World Cup&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I had a tough time searching for a blue map of India online and ended up creating them myself. With this post they are released online; you are free to use them as you may wish. However, a link to this blog is really appreciated (which I&amp;rsquo;m sure none of you are going to do! &amp;#x1f61d; )&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>First Time Clipper Self Haircut</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-time-clipper-self-haircut/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 06:39:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-time-clipper-self-haircut/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>[Dated 12/12/2010; Posted 5/2/2011 due to photos.]&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you think this is a &amp;ldquo;own haircut how to&amp;rdquo;, let me tell you, you&amp;rsquo;ll be disappointed because it is not. However, you can read further to find out my tale with giving myself a haircut for the first time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When I was kid, I had this dream, albeit shot-lived, of becoming an hairstylist. But then I went to college trying to become an engineer! One fine day back from a bad haircut, I was thinking about it and decided to style my own hair for the first time. Just to give it a try! After some thinking, the easiest style was to go bald which is exactly what I used to do back in college; I used to shave my head twice a week and sport a beard. It continued for a couple months not only because I liked it but also due to the over-pouring compliments from friends and all those heads turned! So, this isn&amp;rsquo;t the first time I designed my own hairstyle.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pencil Sketch</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/pencil-sketch-sachin-tendulkar/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 06:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/pencil-sketch-sachin-tendulkar/</guid><description>&lt;p>A pencil sketch of the greatest batsman to ever play the game of Cricket - Sachin Tendulkar. Sketched more than half a decade ago. Does it look like Sachin?&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/26-sketch/Sachin%20Tendulkar.jpg"
 alt="Sachin Tendulkar">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Sachin Tendulkar&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/26-sketch/Sachin%20Tendulkar%20v2.jpg"
 alt="Sachin Tendulkar">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Sachin Tendulkar (scanned and GIMP&amp;rsquo;d)&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Keeping Personal and Technical Blogs Separate</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/keeping-personal-and-technical-blogs-separate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 04:46:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/keeping-personal-and-technical-blogs-separate/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Disclaimer&lt;/strong>: I&amp;rsquo;m no expert in blogging. I do not have much knowledge about the Wordpress framework either. The following post is based on my previous couple of hours of reading on multisite blogging. Feel free to enlighten me in the comment section.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="why">Why?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>If you are starting/have started blogging as a hobby, at first it may seem that having one blog and blogging everything in it is a good idea. However, after sometime you will feel as if you should keep the posts separate and in their own blogs rather than having them all in under one blog. I was no different; I never gave much time to think about it until one of my readers (second category below) sent me a message.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>RSS Feed URL Changed</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/rss-feed-url-changed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 06:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/rss-feed-url-changed/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dear readers,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Though there are only a few of you and I&amp;rsquo;m very sure you are very capable of finding it out yourselves, I think I must save your time and tell you that I&amp;rsquo;m moving my RSS Feed address.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The idea is simple:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>I post this post and then&lt;/li>
&lt;li>change my RSS feed address.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>So that, assuming you miss this post, in case you wonder why you are not finding any new unread items in Lobo&amp;rsquo;s blog feed, this is the post you find on the old feed and you know the answer. I have moved!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Strike Out Corruption In India</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/strike-out-corruption-in-india-support-jan-lokpal-bill/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 07:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/strike-out-corruption-in-india-support-jan-lokpal-bill/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/index_archive/index_004.html">CORRUPTION IN INDIA&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Will Jan Lokpal bill solve the issue? I don&amp;rsquo;t know for sure, but it will definitely set us on the right path by giving more power to those who matter. It&amp;rsquo;s heartening to see India united to fight against the corruption. If an old man [Anna Hazare] can do so much, why can&amp;rsquo;t the youth do more? If you can, &lt;strong>PLEASE SHOW YOUR SUPPORT&lt;/strong> in any way possible. Spread the word.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Indians Are The World Champions</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 06:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/indians-are-the-world-champions/</guid><description>&lt;p>You know by now. Indians are the world champions! Yeah, say that again, WE ARE THE CHAMPIONS!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Remember &amp;ldquo;More than a billion hearts and one shared dream&amp;rdquo;? That&amp;rsquo;s what I &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/">wrote&lt;/a> when the world cup started. That dream has come true! Now more than 50% of Indian population can proudly say they saw their captain lift the world cup at least once in their life. Glory!&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="homepage-mania">Homepage mania:&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>I dedicated the &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/index_archive/index_002.html">homepage&lt;/a> to Green Bay Packers and they won the super bowl; they are the Champions!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Camping At Devil's Lake State Park, Wisconsin</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 07:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/camping-at-devils-lake-state-park-wisconsin/</guid><description>&lt;p>On a Friday&amp;rsquo;s evening, eight of us set out to Devil&amp;rsquo;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin in two cars. We reached when it was dark and setup three tents in two camps. The rain god was happy and decided not to play spoilsport; it poured only when we were in the tent.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/23-devils-lake/basecamp.jpg"
 alt="Tents at Devil&amp;#39;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Tents at Devil&amp;rsquo;s Lake State Park, Wisconsin&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>We setup campfire, prepared dinner. Made s&amp;rsquo;more in the campfire for the first time; I had no clue what s&amp;rsquo;more was!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Year That Was - 2010</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-year-that-was-2010-excerpts-from-the-unborn-posts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 07:09:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-year-that-was-2010-excerpts-from-the-unborn-posts/</guid><description>&lt;p>Year 2010 was a totally different and a very special one for me. It all started in late 2009; from someone who used to talk so less and hardly socialize to wherever I am right now was quite a journey. I had a jolly good time and I wish it is one of the many years to come.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>2010 had some downs, but I hardly remember them. The good ones are so many that I don&amp;rsquo;t have time to recall the bad ones. In fact, I don&amp;rsquo;t even remember many of the good ones. There were a couple of things on my mind in year 2010 which I never posted. I was caught up in a lot of things and never really took time out to do it. Recently, when I was thinking about it, I was in a dilemma whether to post them now or not. Not because I don&amp;rsquo;t remember them but mainly because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to bore you to death (have I?) Anyway, since I&amp;rsquo;m using this blog also as a diary to share things, I will go ahead note them down here. All in one post!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Easiest Way To Solve Rubik's Cube</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/easiest-way-to-solve-rubiks-cube-without-cheating/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 07:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/easiest-way-to-solve-rubiks-cube-without-cheating/</guid><description>&lt;p>The following tutorials/videos helped me a lot in learning to solve the &lt;a href="http://amzn.to/2n0eAsL">3x3 Rubik&amp;rsquo;s Cube&lt;/a>). I think these are the easiest ways to solve the rubik&amp;rsquo;s cube and hope you find it helpful too. You may find that the technique used is the same, just the explanation differs in most of the cases. Second and third videos take different approaches to solve third layer. Latter is easier and has less number of steps.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Skiing on Cascade mountains, Wisconsin</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 04:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-on-cascade-mountains-wisconsin/</guid><description>&lt;p>Another ski trip. This time just for a day. I loved skiing last time so much that when I heard that another group was heading to Cascade Mountains, I simply couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We had two guys who had never skied before so we helped them on the bunny hills and moved on to others slopes. Though I&amp;rsquo;m a newbie I could tell that the snow at &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/">the Ski Brule&lt;/a> was better. At Cascade it was kind of slippery compared to Ski Brule. May be it was due to the weather, it was mid 30s. Duh!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Preparing Chocolate Brownie</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/preparing-chocolate-brownie/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 23:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/preparing-chocolate-brownie/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is Sunday afternoon, I&amp;rsquo;m bored and I&amp;rsquo;m planning to prepare Chocolate Brownies. I have never prepared it before and looking at the instructions on the pack, I must say it is not big deal at all. All you need is, well, &lt;a href="http://amzn.to/2BkwBHq">Chocolate Brownie mix&lt;/a>, some eggs and vegetable oil. I&amp;rsquo;m off.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>PS: Okay, I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything to blog about. Big deal. &amp;#x1f61d;&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/20-brownie/brownie1.JPG"
 alt="Brownies in the tray">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Brownies in the tray&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Ski Trip</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 02:43:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-ski-trip-to-ski-brule-michigan/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/lobo.jpg"
 alt="Lobo(Ski Brule)">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Lobo(Ski Brule)&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/Buckhorn%20Chalet.jpg"
 alt="Buckhorn Chalet">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>Around twenty of us drove up to Ski Brule, Iron River Michigan, on Thursday and stayed at &lt;strong>Buckhorn Chalet&lt;/strong> right in front of the slopes. The slopes looked so beautiful and scary at the same time. I was excited to ski for the first time the very next day.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/19-ski-brule/on%20the%20bunny.jpg"
 alt="With Staff on bunny hills">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>With Staff on bunny hills&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>When we reached there, there was a free lessons for first timers (should register beforehand). The faculty was nice enough to allow me to join even-though I had not registered. They had first-timers-ski-free offer as well which I missed! Anyway, the faculty was helping the inexperienced on the bunny hills in using the ropes, sliding, stopping, turning. They answered my questions, helped me get up, skied down the slope along with me, helped me tremendously in getting used to the rope (this was so difficult at first, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go more than two feet) and were very cheerful. Now when I think of it, I liked the skiing experience because of their good faculty as well. Thumbs up for them. &amp;#x1f44d;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Skiing</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/skiing-whats-the-big-deal/</guid><description>&lt;p>Skiing is fun. As a beginner, it is something you will hate during but love afterward. If you have skied already, you&amp;rsquo;ll easily dismiss me, but if you have not then you&amp;rsquo;ll know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong here, if you have never been skiing before and if you have a chance, just pack up and go. It is fun. It is as much fun to ski as it is pain as a beginner.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>2011 World Cup</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/2011-world-cup-men-in-blue-will-rock-the-world/</guid><description>&lt;p>My dear fellow Indians and everyone,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Remember 1983 Prudential world cup? Remember Captain Kapil Dev&amp;rsquo;s greatest catch that dethroned King Viv? No? Neither do I! It&amp;rsquo;s been 28 years since our captain lifted the cricket world cup. Not just me, nearly 50% of the current Indian population wasn&amp;rsquo;t even born back then!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>More than a billion hearts and one shared dream, to see the men in blue lift the 2011 cricket world cup. Will it come true this time? Let us hope so.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Green Bay Packer on my Homepage</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/green-bay-packer-on-my-homepage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 07:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/green-bay-packer-on-my-homepage/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hello world,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I dedicated my &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/index_archive/index_002.html">homepage&lt;/a> for Green Bay Packers on 6th February, 2011 and what they got me the same day?! THE SUPER BOWL!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>It&amp;rsquo;s hard not to be a packer fan.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/16-superbowl/Packer%20fans%20II.JPG"
 alt="Packer Fans on Super Bowl day">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Packer Fans on Super Bowl day&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/16-superbowl/Packer%20fans%20I.JPG"
 alt="Packer Fans on Super Bowl day">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Packer Fans on Super Bowl day&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/16-superbowl/Vince%20Lombardi%20Trophy%20-%20Superbowl%20XLV.jpg"
 alt="Northwestern Mutual Superbowl XLV celebration - Vince Lombardi Ice Trophy">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Northwestern Mutual Superbowl XLV celebration - Vince Lombardi Ice Trophy&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Northwestern Mutual Supports Green Bay Packers</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 05:42:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/northwestern-mutual-supports-green-bay-packers/</guid><description>&lt;p>Pictures of Northwestern Mutual Insurance company in downtown Milwaukee during NFL 2011 showing support for Green Bay Packers.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/16-superbowl/NM%20East%20Building.jpg"
 alt="Northwestern Mutual East Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Northwestern Mutual East Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/16-superbowl/NM%20South%20Building.jpg"
 alt="Northwestern Mutual South Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Northwestern Mutual South Building lit up to support Packers, Milwaukee&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>Photo courtesy: &lt;a href="sushanthmohan.com">Sushanth Mohan&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Packers, Team Spirit Day</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 07:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/packers-team-spirit-day-pictures-and-more/</guid><description>&lt;p>The whole office was green! Some pictures(scaled down) from the team spirit day mentioned in my previous post.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Lobo.jpg"
 alt="Yours truly">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Yours truly&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Lobo_Rahul.jpg"
 alt="Rahul and I">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Rahul and I&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packer_Lobo_Parth.jpg"
 alt="Parth and I">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Parth and I&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Lobo_Rahul2.jpg"
 alt="Rahul and I, again.">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Rahul and I, again.&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Pravin_Shailesh_Bharath.jpg"
 alt="Pravin, Shailesh, and Bharath">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Pravin, Shailesh, and Bharath&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/14-packers/Packers_Shailesh_Pravin_Bharath.jpg"
 alt="Shailesh, Pravin, and Bharath">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Shailesh, Pravin, and Bharath&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>The game at Major Goolsby&amp;rsquo;s with a couple of my friends - Shailesh, Myself, Balaji, Bharath, Mada, Ramendra (behind the camera).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Bears Still Suck!!!</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-bears-still-suck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 03:35:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/the-bears-still-suck/</guid><description>&lt;p>Green Bay Packers didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint in the playoff; they did just what I hoped for in my previous post, &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/">First Winter in Milwaukee&lt;/a>. They kicked the Bears ass.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I watched the game at Major Goolsby’s with a couple of my friends. Packers played really well in the first and second quarter with a touchdown in each. Then their game was down and they were struggling just like Chicago Bears (but, the bears still suck!). There was nothing in third quarter. Fourth quarter was really intense. The crowd went crazy when Raji touchdown on an interception. The score was 21-7 Packers leading. Bears fought back with a touchdown in next 80 seconds or so taking the score to 21-14.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>First Winter in Milwaukee</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 06:30:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-winter-in-milwaukee/</guid><description>&lt;p>Just when I started to laugh at people who were scaring me about the winter, mother nature made sure I shut up. It was a total pain to walk 6 blocks back home from office today! The main problem is the wind. If it isn&amp;rsquo;t for the wind chill factor, the winter is not much of a problem.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s getting freaking cold here in Milwaukee; it&amp;rsquo;s expected to hit -8°F(-22°C) tomorrow and with the wind and other factors, it&amp;rsquo;s expected to feel like -27°F(-32°C). To say the least, that sucks!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>O_ops: It's Christmas Time</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-its-christmas-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2011 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/oops-its-christmas-time/</guid><description>&lt;p>I had been wondering for a last couple of days if I should start a O_ops series to just list downs things that are O_ops. Then I get this email and here I start!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It was Christmas time and I got an unusual wish from a sweetheart friend of mine.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>From: SS&lt;br>
Sent: Friday, December 24, 2010 5:37 PM&lt;br>
To: Lobo&lt;br>
Subject: Its Christmas time :)&lt;br>
Hey Lobo Marry Christmas&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Working on The Blog</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/working-on-the-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 09:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/working-on-the-blog/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is a perfect example for a seemingly easy task taking up so much of one&amp;rsquo;s time. I have been busy working on this blog for a last couple of days. I spent so much time and yet there are so many things to do!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here is what I have done so far:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Updated feed through &lt;a href="https://feeds.feedburner.com/lobopraveen">FeedBurner&lt;/a>: this was already present, I updated some settings.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Added Google AdSense: there comes a time in everyone&amp;rsquo;s life when they turn greedy. This is my time. &amp;#x1f61b;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>RELATIVE Performance Evaluation</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/relative-performance-evaluation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 23:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/relative-performance-evaluation/</guid><description>&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;">&lt;code class="language-javascript" data-lang="javascript">&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>&lt;span style="color:#66d9ef">if&lt;/span>( parseInt(&lt;span style="color:#e6db74">&amp;#34;1&amp;#34;&lt;/span>) &lt;span style="color:#f92672">===&lt;/span> parseInt(&lt;span style="color:#e6db74">&amp;#34;1+&amp;#34;&lt;/span>) ){
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span> &lt;span style="color:#a6e22e">alert&lt;/span>(&lt;span style="color:#e6db74">&amp;#34;Depends on &amp;#39;the context&amp;#39; and is controlled by external factors!&amp;#34;&lt;/span>);
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>} &lt;span style="color:#66d9ef">else&lt;/span> {
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span> &lt;span style="color:#a6e22e">alert&lt;/span>(&lt;span style="color:#e6db74">&amp;#34;Loser!&amp;#34;&lt;/span>);
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>}
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>&lt;span style="color:#a6e22e">alert&lt;/span>(&lt;span style="color:#e6db74">&amp;#34;Think again!&amp;#34;&lt;/span>);&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Penny Auction Sites</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 21:20:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/penny-auction-sites/</guid><description>&lt;p>Okay, you must have landed here through some search engine while trying to figure out a way to make a fortune by spending pennies. Those &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bidding_fee_auction">penny auction sites&lt;/a> are amazing, aren&amp;rsquo;t they? The concept is so clear and it almost sounds like anyone can get one of those shiny new iPads, Macs, Nikkon D90, or Canon EOS 7D on auction just for a few pennies.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you haven&amp;rsquo;t got a clue about it, I urge you to read about them. READ ABOUT THEM. DO NOT JUMP INTO BIDDING! I mean, I&amp;rsquo;m just saying. If you want go ahead and spend some money; however, do not hold me responsible for any damage. I have already shouted at you. You are lucky that I warned you; It&amp;rsquo;s kind of sad that nobody warned me!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Happy New Year</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/happy-new-year-2011/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 08:30:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/happy-new-year-2011/</guid><description>&lt;p>I think, this is the first time I was out on the new year (January 1st 00:00:00 to be precise). Either I used to be at home or with family in the Church at this time every year. Had loads of fun last few moments of 2010 and enjoyed starting of 2011 with friends at Whiskey Bar in Milwaukee.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Not sure why I&amp;rsquo;m blogging about it but hey this is my blog and I&amp;rsquo;ll post whatever I want&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Holiday Gift 2010</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holiday-gift-2010-organ-donor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 07:48:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holiday-gift-2010-organ-donor/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/13-donor/dl.jpg"
 alt="Driving License">
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any problem communicating it to Mom. She knew it since I was 10 years old or so. I had told her about this wish and so did she. We both want not just organs but entire body to be donated when we pass away.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This is a picture of an eye donation card I signed nearly 15 years ago! (I must have been 10 years old or so.) I still have it in my wallet, I know it carries little value but I still keep it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Password Change</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/password-change-identifying-the-weakest-link-in-the-chain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 08:15:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/password-change-identifying-the-weakest-link-in-the-chain/</guid><description>&lt;p>Last evening, I changed my passwords on all accounts on all websites that I frequent. Just curious to know how many did the same. Hopefully someone will come up with the stats soon.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I always use different passwords on different sites. All of them are at least 10+ character long with minimum one capital, special character, and number in it. Curious to know what my friends do, I brought up this topic briefly. After the discussion, I realized that even those who are into IT, IS, computers etc. use simple, stupid passwords. Most of them even create documents with the id, password combinations and store them on their desktop! Guess what, their systems are not even encrypted!!! When you tell them about the seriousness of the issue, they just look at me and say, &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not dealing with that important data here&amp;rsquo; or &amp;rsquo;nerd&amp;rsquo; or something similar.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Thanksgiving 2010 - A Long Weekend</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/thanksgiving-2010-a-long-weekend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 01:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/thanksgiving-2010-a-long-weekend/</guid><description>&lt;p>A long weekend (four days) - many of my friends are on trips visiting places. I&amp;rsquo;m sitting here writing this post! I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go due to work. I had to work for a couple of hours exactly in the middle of the four days so I stayed back. It sure doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel good but not as bad as I imagined it to be. Almost 3/4th of the long weekend has gone by. It&amp;rsquo;s work and someone had to do it. Moreover, it&amp;rsquo;s because of work I&amp;rsquo;m here in US in the first place so no whining.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Eat Oatmeal Idiots</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/eat-oatmeal-idiots/</guid><description>&lt;p>I know, the subject is a bit harsh, but it&amp;rsquo;s well suited for all comments I get from my room-mates about eating oats. Oats is one of the food that I just love. I first started having oatmeal three years ago when I came across many articles on the net. I felt like, it was made for me! Why? It&amp;rsquo;s simple, easy to prepare, healthy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Believe it or not with very little or no exercise I was able to cut down all fat and lose weight just by controlling eating habits. Needless to say one of the main ingredients (and the only one for sometime) being oats!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Walk of Life</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/walk-of-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 16:36:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/walk-of-life/</guid><description>&lt;p>This morning on my way to office I saw an old couple walking across the street. The gentleman was walking at a-couple-inches-a-step pace and the lady, it seemed like, was moving only an inch with every single step. They were crossing a relatively free street and he was holding her hands and leading her. They crossed the street and then turned left to cross another one. A few cars stopped in front of them. Finally, they crossed the street and reached diagonally opposite side of the junction from where they started.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Culinary Skills - III</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-iii/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 05:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-iii/</guid><description>&lt;p>Another one from the old drafts. Only pictures this time. :-)&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/11-cooking/3_1.jpg"
 alt="1">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Step 1&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/11-cooking/3_2.jpg"
 alt="2">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Step 2&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/11-cooking/3_3.jpg"
 alt="3">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Step 3&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/11-cooking/3_4.jpg"
 alt="4">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Step 4&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/11-cooking/3_5.jpg"
 alt="5">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Step 5&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Halloween 2010 - more pics</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010-more-pics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 01:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010-more-pics/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/10-halloween/pic2.JPG"
 alt="V and Evey">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>V and Evey&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/10-halloween/last.JPG"
 alt="Hey, that&amp;#39;s not!">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Hey, that&amp;rsquo;s not!&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>I was once told that people lose their inhibitions when they are behind the mask. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I agree completely.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Halloween 2010</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 03:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/halloween-2010/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dear blog, as you know, uh oh you don&amp;rsquo;t, do you? I never mentioned about it! I&amp;rsquo;m in US right now. The very fact that I haven&amp;rsquo;t mentioned it till now shows how busy I&amp;rsquo;m here! Naah, not really, that&amp;rsquo;s what I say when I turn lazy and forget about you. I won&amp;rsquo;t promise you that I won&amp;rsquo;t again; I can&amp;rsquo;t keep such promises. Sorry!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anyway, this is kind of new. Different lifestyles. Cultures. New friends. Work environment. Schedules. Meetings. Food. Currency. Everything. To some extent, I&amp;rsquo;m leading a different kind of a life which I don&amp;rsquo;t exactly prefer but don&amp;rsquo;t mind trying for some more time.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Culinary Skills - II</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-ii/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2010 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-ii/</guid><description>&lt;p>This was in draft mode for over 5 months now! There is something with me and updating this blog. There are a couple of more drafts. I plan to post all of them in next two weeks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If I&amp;rsquo;m not following the recipes which I read somewhere, I will keep it very simple. First I check what are the items I can use, then etch a plan, pick the items, and cook. That is exactly what I did today. The recipes are very simple and I&amp;rsquo;m not going to type it - I&amp;rsquo;m a little bored to do that now. May be some other day.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cricket: India versus USA</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 04:28:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/cricket-india-versus-usa/</guid><description>&lt;p>It was about a month after the softball match between &lt;em>India and USA&lt;/em>, the Americans wanted to try a match of Cricket. Rightly so, Cricket to Americans is like softball to Indians. We did have a match and due to less attendance on USA team, it was played after shuffling the teams.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/09-cricket/Cricket_1.jpg"
 alt="Cricket: India vs USA">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Cricket: India vs USA&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/09-cricket/Cricket_2.jpg"
 alt="Cricket: India vs USA">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Cricket: India vs USA&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/09-cricket/Cricket_3.jpg"
 alt="Cricket: India vs USA">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Cricket: India vs USA&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>From India To USA</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-india-to-usa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 05:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/from-india-to-usa/</guid><description>&lt;p>I can write a detailed travelogue, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to bore you to death! I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m good at writing! Here is the short version! &amp;#x1f603;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A weeks notice was all I got about my first ever business trip. To work at client&amp;rsquo;s location, to deal with client interaction, to deal with the cultural differences, and the list goes on. Though I was prepared for all of it, I was caught off guard with other stuff.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Last Day at the Dance Class</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/last-day-at-the-dance-class/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 06:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/last-day-at-the-dance-class/</guid><description>&lt;p>A little sadness has taken over me. Today was my last day at Dance Verve. Remember &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-week-that-was/">this last paragraph&lt;/a>? A week after that I joined Dance Verve at BTM Check Post.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I remember the very first day - I entered the class when Taj Khan (we call him sir) was not yet in. I talked to two guys (now I know them - Pavan and Manas) and sir arrived in about 15 minutes. He asked to join right then as I introduced myself. Somehow I was still very nervous and said I&amp;rsquo;d join from the next day. I didn&amp;rsquo;t forget to mention that I had never danced before (of course Salsa apart) and I tried may times and failed miserably. I used to get very conscious. He just smiled and said, it will take sometime before I can dance and I should be regular.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hands of God</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hands-of-god/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 21:51:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/hands-of-god/</guid><description>&lt;p>Uruguay vs. Ghana
Quarter final match - 2010 FIFA World Cup&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I was sleepy, but somehow this match seemed too good to miss. I had to wash my face with cold water to stay awake. I must tell you, it was WORTH it. Much much more than WORTH it. An exciting match. Last few moments I had my heart in my mouth. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t supporting any of the teams, but still I feel heartbroken; Ghana should have won. Unfair.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Planned Visit Gone Wrong</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-planned-visit-gone-wrong/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 17:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-planned-visit-gone-wrong/</guid><description>&lt;h5 id="15th-july-2010-early-morning-">15th July 2010 Early morning –&lt;/h5>
&lt;p>The shopkeeper A got a shocker when he opened the door. Some items inside the shop were displaced, the drawer opened, 200 Rupees missing. He informed my Dad - the shop owner. Since the door was locked and there was no sign of any damage to the door or the locks they decided that somebody has access to the keys or someone has got the duplicates done. They decide to change the locks and drop the issue because going to the police for a mere 200 Rupees is stupidity they thought and they might have to spend a lot more than that if they call the police!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Culinary Skills - I</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-i/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 20:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-culinary-skills-i/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/07-chicken-dry/start.jpg"
 alt="Keep the ingredients ready">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Keep the ingredients ready&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>I wanted to show off my culinary skill (if I have any &amp;#x1f61b;) the other day when I made a chicken dish, unfortunately, I forgot to post it. This was in draft mode for over 5 months now! I had completely forgotten about it until yesterday when I started preparing biriyani. Publishing it now, enjoy. &amp;#x1f603;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If I&amp;rsquo;m not following the recipes, I will keep it very simple. First, I check what are the items I can use, then etch a plan, pick the items, and cook. That is exactly what I did in these two occasions. The recipe was very simple but I don&amp;rsquo;t remember it now!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My H1B Visa Stamping Saga - Part II</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 19:05:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-ii/</guid><description>&lt;p>The day of stamping - My interview was schedule at 8:30AM and I was expected to be there by 8AM. The previous day night I set alarm for 6, 6:10, 6:15AM. My usual pattern even after which I don&amp;rsquo;t wake up! I slept through all three alarms and woke up when Mom called me to wish me at 7AM. The cab guy also called at the same time. Cleverly, I had ironed clothes and arranged documents in Bangalore itself; I got ready in just about 15 minutes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My H1B Visa stamping Saga - Part I</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 17:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/my-h1b-visa-stamping-saga-part-i/</guid><description>&lt;p>My H1B visa was approved in December 2009 and finally, I got to get it stamped on 18th May 2010. I had arranged all documents by last Thursday and booked air tickets to Chennai. I had never travelled by air before; it was going to be my first time. &amp;#x1f603;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Monday morning I got a call from the cab driver who was lost trying to find me! After around 6-7 call and giving him directions, he finally made it. Travel to airport took nearly 1.5 hours and there was never a boring moment; he was more talkative than I&amp;rsquo;m.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Childhood memories</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/childhood-memories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 17:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/childhood-memories/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m feeling nostalgic today. Very much. I had lot of time at my hand and decided to clean up my cupboard, which I do from time to time. Until a few years back, I used to keep all things I used to have during my childhood days and one day I decided to get rid of all the junk. First time I did it, believe me, it was so painful. Each small item had so many memories associated with it, but I had to clean up stuff.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Quit Smoking</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/quit-smoking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 18:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/quit-smoking/</guid><description>&lt;p>I started smoking, I guess, eight or nine years ago. For the initial four or five years it was more or less like two or three cigarettes a year, so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t a smoker then by any standard. :o) However, I really started smoking nearly three years ago.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I have been on and off at it. I quit smoking for a couple of months a couple of times in these three years. The longest period was around six months. I was very convinced that I&amp;rsquo;d never smoke again until one day, in late 2009, when a friend of mine asked me to accompany him to the smoking area (Anna shop next to &lt;a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/Infosys&amp;#43;Limited/@12.9047813,74.8363542,15z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x0:0xdfdd5d7661b0cb5!8m2!3d12.9047813!4d74.8363542?sa=X&amp;amp;ved=0ahUKEwi9rKnUxPzZAhVG7VMKHUjFB78Q_BIItQEwDg">Infosys Mangalore DC&lt;/a>). Unfortunately, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t refuse when he offered me a cigarette. After that there was no looking back, I had on an average one a day!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>BBMP Elections and Women Reservation</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/bbmp-elections-and-women-reservation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 19:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/bbmp-elections-and-women-reservation/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bruhat_Bengaluru_Mahanagara_Palike">BBMP&lt;/a> elections are scheduled for tomorrow. My ward is one of those wards reserved for women. That is nothing to be happy about! Reservation is a very noble plan with a pathetic implementation. I was trying to get as much information about the candidates as possible so that I can vote for the most eligible. There are seven women candidates contesting in the election from my ward. As far as I could see, all of them are wives or relatives of politically powerful men and I find most of them incapable!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>First Glass Painting</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-glass-painting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/first-glass-painting/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is the glass painting I was talking about &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-week-that-was/">here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/04-glass-painting/GlassPainting_01.jpg"
 alt="Lord Ganesha">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Lord Ganesha&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>The following two are made(on the window) by my brother.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/04-glass-painting/GlassPainting_Bro_01.jpg"
 alt="Glass painting on the window">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Glass painting on the window&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/04-glass-painting/GlassPainting_Bro_02.jpg"
 alt="Glass painting on the window">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>Glass painting on the window&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>A Week That Was</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-week-that-was/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 19:33:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-week-that-was/</guid><description>&lt;p>Last week was the crappiest of all, but it ended in a good note. It oscillated between okay to bad, bad to worse, and back to okay and then to good. First two days were uneventful and I had no clue of what lie ahead.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Wednesday was the beginning. Firstly, a brand new system welcomed me to office on Wednesday morning; they had formatted my machine without any kind of confirmation. Secondly, two priority-one production issues on Thursday and some actions taken to resolve the issues came back on Friday as a different issue. To top it all, I had to deal with it using a newly installed operating system. No links, no data, no mail archives, and no software. Only notepad and the damned communicator which kept pissing me off! This whole thing happened in the same week in which I failed in a certification, which I&amp;rsquo;m not worried about, and a written test.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Weekend In Mangalore</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 15:34:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/a-weekend-in-mangalore/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Update (2018): TMI galore!&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Mangalore. Stirs up a lot of feeling. The first city, other than Bangalore, where I spent more than a year, the city where I lived independently, the city where I gained financial independence, the city where I started watching movies (for real!), the city which has given me a few best friends, the city where I fell in love&amp;hellip; I have so many fond memories of this city that I could go on and on and on. But this post is about my visit to Mangalore last weekend.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Highest Runs In An ODI Match – Sachin Tendulkar</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/highest-runs-in-an-odi-match-sachin-tendulkar/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 04:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/highest-runs-in-an-odi-match-sachin-tendulkar/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have come across a lot of comments, communications, posts, and people (even my Dad and Bro) where they mention how they hated a Pakistani cricketer(Saeed Anwar) holding the record for highest ODI runs in a match. I don&amp;rsquo;t understand! A cricketer is a cricketer, a game is a game, a record is a record, what does it have to do with the citizenship?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What would you(esp. Indians) have called Sachin, if he was a Pakistani? A devil? &lt;strong>&lt;em>=P&lt;/em>&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Valentine's Day Gift</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/valentines-day-gift/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 18:18:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/valentines-day-gift/</guid><description>&lt;p>This valentine&amp;rsquo;s day she was very happy. She has been with me for quite long time now; I had never seen her so happy and excited in before. As I type this post she is on call and I can clearly hear her sharing it with her sister and this is her third call! &lt;strong>&lt;em>:o)&lt;/em>&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Though she&amp;rsquo;d never tell me, I always knew that she wanted it. She is very interested in stitching, embroidery, and other creative stuff which mainly deals with fabric. She does stitch clothes at a very low price for poor women who work at construction sites. She never got support in terms of money, encouragement, or time to learn.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>3 Nuts</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/3-nuts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 19:43:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/3-nuts/</guid><description>&lt;p>The title is inspired by the movie &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/3_Idiots">3 Idiots&lt;/a> which the world around me is going gaga over. The picture was clicked over the weekend with a point &amp;amp; shoot camera when I was going mad with boredom. Reason for posting this? I don&amp;rsquo;t know! I started experimenting with GIMP and I have provided both versions of the picture.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/01-nuts/3Nuts1.jpg"
 alt="3 nuts - Unedited">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>3 nuts - Unedited&lt;/p>
 &lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/01-nuts/3Nuts.jpg"
 alt="3 nuts - Edited">&lt;figcaption>
 &lt;p>3 nuts - Edited&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Good Physique &amp; Polio-stricken Chicken's Leg</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/good-physique-polio-stricken-chickens-leg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 07:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/good-physique-polio-stricken-chickens-leg/</guid><description>&lt;p>I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether to be happy or doubtful when a stranger walks up to me in the gym and&lt;/p>
&lt;div class='convo'>
 &lt;ol>
 
 
 
 
 &lt;li>
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='person'>Stranger&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='sep'> : &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class='text'>Hey&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 &lt;/li>
 
 
 
 &lt;li>
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='person'>Me&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='sep'> : &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class='text'>Hi&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 &lt;/li>
 
 
 
 &lt;li>
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='person'>Stranger&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='sep'> : &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class='text'>You are regular here?&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 &lt;/li>
 
 
 
 &lt;li>
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='person'>Me&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='sep'> : &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class='text'>(have you ever seen me here earlier?) No. Second day in this gym.&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 &lt;/li>
 
 
 
 &lt;li>
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='person'>Stranger&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='sep'> : &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class='text'>Oh okay.&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 &lt;/li>
 
 
 
 &lt;li>
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='person'>Me&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='sep'> : &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class='text'>Why?&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 &lt;/li>
 
 
 
 &lt;li>
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='person'>Stranger&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='sep'> : &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class='text'>You have got a good physique dude. (smiles)&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 &lt;/li>
 
 
 
 &lt;li>
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='person'>Me&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;div class='sep'> : &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class='text'>Aha, thanks buddy! (flees the scene)&lt;/div>
 
 
 
 &lt;/li>
 
 
 
 
 &lt;/ol>
&lt;/div>

&lt;p>This has happened a couple of times before; back then it was my friends/acquaintances and I knew I deserved it! :o)  But now? Gentleman, you are either trying to motivate me or hitting on me!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Yet Another "Hello, world!"?</title><link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/yet-another-hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 19:31:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/yet-another-hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;div class='align-center'>
 &lt;figure>&lt;img src="https://praveenlobo.com/media/00-25/00-bday/Bday.jpg"
 alt="Happy Birthday!">
&lt;/figure>

&lt;/div>

&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m bored of &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hello_world_program">Hello, world!&lt;/a>; I did that over&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>9000 days&lt;/li>
&lt;li>1300 weeks&lt;/li>
&lt;li>200,000 hours&lt;/li>
&lt;li>13,000,000 minutes&lt;/li>
&lt;li>750,000,000 seconds&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>ago. Yeah, about 25 years ago, I did my personal &lt;em>Hello, world!&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Hello, world!&lt;/p>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Yet another &amp;ldquo;Hello, world!&amp;rdquo;? Yes, this time not from me but from this very blog you are reading! &lt;strong>&lt;em>:o)&lt;/em>&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On a serious note, I&amp;rsquo;m very happy to start this blog, it was one of the items pending on my &lt;a href="https://praveenlobo.com/bucket-list/">Bucket List&lt;/a> for a long time now. Keep watching this space for the list!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>