<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rant on Praveen Lobo</title>
    <link>https://praveenlobo.com/tags/rant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rant on Praveen Lobo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 20:58:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://praveenlobo.com/tags/rant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HOLY CRAP!!!</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holy-crap-missing-in-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 20:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/holy-crap-missing-in-action/</guid>
      <description>HOLY MOTHER OF SWEET BABY CORN! It has seriously been a long while! 3 years? 4 years? Surprised the blog still exists! LOL! Actually not that much surprised. I pay every year to renew hosting so I know it exists! 😛
The TODO list thing I do. Seriously, it has gotten out of hand! I have unfinished drafts from 2011, 2012, 2013 which are still not posted! I feel embarrassed; at the same time I feel overwhelmed thinking how fast the time flies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Have I Been Up To This Summer?</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 17:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/what-have-i-been-up-to-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>It has been a long time since I blogged regularly. We have a couple of weeks of summer left in 2012 and I don’t want to waste that spending more time on blogging. Lately, I have been feeling like blogging is a winter activity (not saying that I blog regularly in winter). There are a number of topics blog about but no time. I keep adding topics to the todo list and keep deleting when I revisit because it’s either too late or it is making the list too big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daylight Saving Time (DST)</title>
      <link>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/daylight-saving-time-dst-should-be-a-part-of-our-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 02:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://praveenlobo.com/blog/daylight-saving-time-dst-should-be-a-part-of-our-history/</guid>
      <description>I was having a conversation with a friend of mine who is convinced that the Daylight Saving Time (DST) change is good and makes perfect sense. I, for one, think that the DST is not useful anymore and it could have been avoided altogether. Just imagine if we didn’t have clocks and a way to time. We would have adjusted our lifestyles automatically to adapt to the nature. Instead of adjusting the clock, we should have adjusted the schedules.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>